<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure virtual network on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/azure-virtual-network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure virtual network on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/azure-virtual-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Your Local Sites to Azure Using Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/connecting_your_local_sites_to_azure_using_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/connecting_your_local_sites_to_azure_using_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Azure Virtual WAN is a networking service that provides a simple, unified, and global connectivity solution for connecting your on-premises sites to Azure. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how you can leverage Virtual WAN to establish secure site-to-site VPN connections between your local network and your Azure resources.
Understanding Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a fully managed, software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) service that simplifies the process of connecting your branch offices, retail locations, and other remote sites to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Remote Access to Azure Resources Using Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_remote_access_to_azure_resources_using_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_remote_access_to_azure_resources_using_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Secure Remote Access to Azure Resources Using Azure Virtual WAN In today&amp;rsquo;s increasingly distributed work environment, providing secure remote access to corporate resources has become a critical priority for organizations. Azure Virtual WAN offers a powerful solution to this challenge, enabling you to create point-to-site (P2S) User VPN connections that allow remote users to securely access your Azure resources.
Overview of Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a networking service that simplifies the creation and management of wide-area networks (WANs).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
