<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Cost Management on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/cloud-cost-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Cost Management on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/cloud-cost-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Microsoft Cost Management- Optimize Your Cloud Spending</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_microsoft_cost_management_optimize_your_cloud_spending/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_microsoft_cost_management_optimize_your_cloud_spending/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Cost Management is a powerful suite of FinOps tools that empowers organizations to analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud costs. This comprehensive platform provides a centralized view of your cloud spending, enabling you to make data-driven decisions and achieve cost optimization at scale.
Understanding the Commerce Data Pipeline At the core of Cost Management is the Microsoft Commerce data pipeline, which processes and tracks all commercial transactions, from consumer to enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Your FinOps Practice with Improved Azure Cost Management Exports</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</guid>
      <description>Azure&amp;rsquo;s Cost Management service has recently introduced an &amp;ldquo;Improved Exports&amp;rdquo; experience that aims to simplify and enhance the process of exporting cost and usage data for FinOps professionals. This new feature offers a range of improvements designed to help organizations better manage their cloud spending and optimize their cloud investments.
The Improved Exports experience provides several key benefits:
Expanded Dataset Support The enhanced exports feature now supports a wider range of datasets, including price sheets, reservation recommendations, reservation details, and reservation transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
