<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Adoption Framework on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/cloud-adoption-framework/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Adoption Framework on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/cloud-adoption-framework/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Your Cloud Adoption with the Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/accelerate_your_cloud_adoption_with_the_cloud_adoption_framework_for_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/accelerate_your_cloud_adoption_with_the_cloud_adoption_framework_for_azure/</guid>
      <description>The Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure is a comprehensive set of tools, templates, and assessments that can help you quickly implement technical changes and accelerate your cloud adoption journey. This framework covers various phases of the cloud adoption process, from strategy and planning to readiness, governance, migration, innovation, and management.
Strategy The Cloud Adoption Framework offers several resources to help you define and refine your cloud adoption strategy:
 Cloud Adoption Strategy Evaluator assessment: Assess your current cloud adoption strategy and get recommendations on building and advancing your cloud business case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Journey with the Microsoft Cloud Adoption Framework</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_with_the_microsoft_cloud_adoption_framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_with_the_microsoft_cloud_adoption_framework/</guid>
      <description>As organizations increasingly embrace cloud computing, their journey towards cloud adoption becomes more complex. The introduction to the hybrid and multicloud scenario outlined in the provided content consolidates various technical and non-technical considerations required to prepare for this journey.
The key focus of this scenario is to enable two primary outcomes:
 Hybrid and Multicloud Adoption: Building, deploying, and/or migrating solutions that are portable, allowing for ease of movement between cloud platforms with minimum vendor lock-in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Your Environment for a Hybrid and Multicloud Future with Azure Arc</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_a_hybrid_and_multicloud_future_with_azure_arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_a_hybrid_and_multicloud_future_with_azure_arc/</guid>
      <description>The modern business landscape demands flexibility, scalability, and seamless integration across on-premises, edge, and multicloud environments. As organizations navigate this complex landscape, the Cloud Adoption Framework&amp;rsquo;s Ready methodology can be a powerful guide, helping you prepare your environment for a successful hybrid and multicloud strategy.
At the heart of this approach are Azure landing zones - the building blocks of any Azure cloud adoption environment. These landing zones account for crucial elements like scale, security governance, networking, identity, cost management, and monitoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud Adoption Framework- A Comprehensive Guide to Successful Azure Migrations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_successful_azure_migrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_successful_azure_migrations/</guid>
      <description>Migrating workloads to the cloud can be a complex and daunting task, but with the right approach and guidance, it can be a seamless and rewarding experience. The Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure provides a comprehensive methodology to help organizations navigate the migration process and ensure a successful transition to the cloud.
The framework outlines four key stages in the migration journey: Prepare, Assess, Deploy, and Release. Each stage is designed to address the unique challenges and considerations that arise throughout the migration process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud Adoption Framework- A Comprehensive Guide to Migrating Workloads to Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_migrating_workloads_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_migrating_workloads_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Migrating workloads to the cloud can be a complex and daunting task, but with the right framework and guidance, it can be a seamless and successful experience. The Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure provides a comprehensive and proven methodology to help organizations plan, prepare, and execute their cloud migration journey.
In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the key stages of the migration process and explore how the Cloud Adoption Framework can help you navigate each step with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Your Environment for Hybrid and Multicloud Scenarios with Azure Arc</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_hybrid_and_multicloud_scenarios_with_azure_arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_hybrid_and_multicloud_scenarios_with_azure_arc/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s ever-evolving technology landscape, organizations are increasingly adopting hybrid and multicloud strategies to meet their diverse business needs. The Cloud Adoption Framework&amp;rsquo;s Ready methodology provides a structured approach to prepare your environment for these complex scenarios, with Azure landing zones serving as the building blocks.
Understanding Hybrid and Multicloud in Azure Landing Zones Azure landing zones are the result of a multi-subscription Azure environment that accounts for scale, security governance, networking, identity, cost management, and monitoring.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
