<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Defender for Containers on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/microsoft-defender-for-containers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft Defender for Containers on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/microsoft-defender-for-containers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Containers Across Clouds with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_containers_across_clouds_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_containers_across_clouds_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is the cloud-native solution for securing your containers, whether they&amp;rsquo;re running in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS), Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE), or on-premises Kubernetes clusters using Azure Arc.
Defender for Containers provides a comprehensive set of security capabilities to protect your container-based applications, including:
Cloud Security Posture Management (CSPM):
 Assess and strengthen the security configuration of your cloud resources Manage compliance against critical industry and regulatory standards  Cloud Workload Protection (CWP):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Containerized Applications with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_containerized_applications_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_containerized_applications_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This powerful platform provides a range of security capabilities to help you protect your Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images.
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers offers both agentless and sensor-based capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your containerized environment:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Containerized Assets with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containerized_assets_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containerized_assets_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses four core domains of container security:
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers offers both agentless and sensor-based capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your containerized environment:
Agentless Capabilities:
 Agentless Discovery for Kubernetes: Provides zero-footprint, API-based discovery of your Kubernetes clusters, their configurations, and deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Your Containerized Infrastructure with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive, cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets, including Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images, across multicloud and on-premises environments.
Four Core Domains of Container Security Defender for Containers assists you with four key areas of container security:
  Security Posture Management:
 Provides continuous monitoring of cloud and Kubernetes APIs to discover resources, offer comprehensive inventory capabilities, detect misconfigurations, and provide guidelines to mitigate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Container Security with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_container_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_container_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses four core domains of container security: security posture management, vulnerability assessment, runtime threat protection, and deployment and monitoring.
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides agentless capabilities that enable zero-footprint, API-based discovery of your Kubernetes clusters, their configurations, and deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Guide to Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Microsoft Defender for Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses the unique security challenges associated with the rapid growth and adoption of containers and Kubernetes.
Defender for Containers provides a holistic approach to container security, focusing on four core domains:
  Security Posture Management: Continuously monitors cloud APIs, Kubernetes APIs, and Kubernetes workloads to discover resources, detect misconfigurations, provide risk assessment, and enable enhanced risk hunting capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Azure Containers with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution designed to enhance the security of your containerized workloads across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your Kubernetes clusters, container registries, container images, and more.
Gain Visibility and Control Over Your Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers offers a range of powerful features to protect your containerized assets:
  Cloud Security Posture Management (CSPM): Defender for Containers provides both foundational and advanced CSPM capabilities, enabling you to continuously assess your security posture, receive security recommendations, and benchmark your cloud security against industry standards across Azure, AWS, and Google Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Microsoft Defender for Containers to Secure Your AWS Workloads</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_microsoft_defender_for_containers_to_secure_your_aws_workloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_microsoft_defender_for_containers_to_secure_your_aws_workloads/</guid>
      <description>Securing Containers in a Multicloud Environment with Microsoft Defender for Containers As organizations increasingly adopt container technologies and deploy workloads across multiple cloud providers, ensuring the security and visibility of these environments becomes a critical priority. Microsoft Defender for Containers, part of the Microsoft Defender for Cloud solution, provides a comprehensive, cloud-native approach to securing containers across Azure, AWS, and other cloud platforms.
Enabling Defender for Containers for Your AWS Accounts To get started with protecting your AWS-hosted containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to enable the Defender for Containers plan within your Microsoft Defender for Cloud environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Container Workloads with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This article delves into the key capabilities of Defender for Containers and how it can help organizations address the evolving security challenges surrounding container-based solutions.
Core Elements of Defender for Containers Defender for Containers assists you with four core domains of container security:
1. Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides a range of agentless capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your container environments:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Amazon Web Service (AWS) Containers with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_amazon_web_service_aws_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_amazon_web_service_aws_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Securing Your Amazon Web Service (AWS) Containers with Microsoft Defender for Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers is a cloud-native solution that helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your Kubernetes clusters, containers, and their applications across multi-cloud and hybrid environments.
Prerequisites Before you can enable Defender for Containers on your AWS account, make sure you have:
 A Microsoft Azure subscription. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you can sign up for a free Azure subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
