<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Multicloud Security on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/multicloud-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Multicloud Security on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/multicloud-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Microsoft Defender for Containers to Secure Your AWS Workloads</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_microsoft_defender_for_containers_to_secure_your_aws_workloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_microsoft_defender_for_containers_to_secure_your_aws_workloads/</guid>
      <description>Securing Containers in a Multicloud Environment with Microsoft Defender for Containers As organizations increasingly adopt container technologies and deploy workloads across multiple cloud providers, ensuring the security and visibility of these environments becomes a critical priority. Microsoft Defender for Containers, part of the Microsoft Defender for Cloud solution, provides a comprehensive, cloud-native approach to securing containers across Azure, AWS, and other cloud platforms.
Enabling Defender for Containers for Your AWS Accounts To get started with protecting your AWS-hosted containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to enable the Defender for Containers plan within your Microsoft Defender for Cloud environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender for Cloud Pricing- Comprehensive Security at Scale</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/microsoft_defender_for_cloud_pricing_comprehensive_security_at_scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/microsoft_defender_for_cloud_pricing_comprehensive_security_at_scale/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Cloud is a unified, cloud-native security platform that provides advanced protection for your multicloud and hybrid environments. With flexible pricing options, you can tailor your security coverage to your specific needs and budget.
Cloud Security Posture Management (CSPM) Microsoft Defender for Cloud offers both foundational and advanced CSPM capabilities:
 Foundational CSPM: This is available for free and includes continuous security assessments, security recommendations, Secure Score, and the Microsoft cloud security benchmark across Azure, AWS, and Google Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
