<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manage Users and Groups with Security Groups in Azure DevOps</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_users_and_groups_with_security_groups_in_azure_devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_users_and_groups_with_security_groups_in_azure_devops/</guid>
      <description>Effectively managing permissions and access in Azure DevOps is key to ensuring your teams can collaborate efficiently and securely. One of the most powerful tools for this is the use of security groups, which allow you to centrally define and control permissions for users and groups.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to leverage security groups in Azure DevOps to streamline user management, assign permissions, and maintain control over your organization&amp;rsquo;s resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Visual Studio Code on Linux- A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_visual_studio_code_on_linux_a_step-by-step_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_visual_studio_code_on_linux_a_step-by-step_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Visual Studio Code on Linux: A Step-by-Step Guide As a developer, having a powerful and customizable code editor is essential. Visual Studio Code (VS Code) has become a popular choice among Linux users due to its cross-platform capabilities, rich feature set, and the strong support of the open-source community. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the steps to set up and configure VS Code on your Linux system, empowering you to unlock the full potential of this versatile code editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Who Can Create Microsoft 365 Groups</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_who_can_create_microsoft_365_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_who_can_create_microsoft_365_groups/</guid>
      <description>In the modern workplace, collaboration is key to driving innovation and productivity. Microsoft 365 Groups are a powerful tool that allow teams to easily share files, communicate, and work together. However, as an administrator, you may need to control who can create these groups to ensure they align with your organization&amp;rsquo;s governance policies.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the steps to manage who can create Microsoft 365 Groups in your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Slack Messaging with PowerShell- The Send-SlackMsg Cmdlet</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_slack_messaging_with_powershell_the_send-slackmsg_cmdlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_slack_messaging_with_powershell_the_send-slackmsg_cmdlet/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced business landscape, effective communication is paramount. As teams become more distributed and remote work becomes the norm, tools like Slack have emerged as essential collaboration platforms. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the power of the Send-SlackMsg PowerShell cmdlet, which allows you to seamlessly integrate Slack messaging into your automation workflows.
Introducing Send-SlackMsg The Send-SlackMsg cmdlet is a powerful tool that enables you to send simple message responses through the Slack Real-Time Messaging (RTM) API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building PowerShell on macOS- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Building PowerShell on macOS: A Comprehensive Guide Building PowerShell on macOS is a straightforward process, but there are a few important steps to keep in mind. This guide will walk you through the entire process, from setting up your development environment to building and running PowerShell on your macOS machine.
Prerequisites Before you begin, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have a few things installed on your macOS system:
 Homebrew or MacPorts, which are package managers for macOS that will help you install the necessary dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Microsoft Teams PowerShell- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_teams_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_teams_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Teams has become an essential communication and collaboration platform for organizations of all sizes. To effectively manage and configure Teams at scale, administrators often turn to PowerShell, a powerful scripting language that provides a wide range of tools and cmdlets for automating various tasks. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the process of installing and utilizing the Microsoft Teams PowerShell module, equipping you with the knowledge and skills to streamline your Teams management effortlessly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Microsoft 365 Group Creation- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/controlling_microsoft_365_group_creation_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/controlling_microsoft_365_group_creation_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Controlling Microsoft 365 Group Creation: A Comprehensive Guide By default, all Microsoft 365 users have the ability to create groups, which can be a beneficial approach as it allows for seamless collaboration without the need for extensive IT involvement. However, in some business scenarios, you may need to restrict who can create these groups to maintain control and ensure compliance with your organization&amp;rsquo;s standards.
Restricting Group Creation If your organization requires tighter control over group creation, you can restrict Microsoft 365 Groups creation to the members of a specific Microsoft 365 group or security group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize Your Azure Resources with Management Groups</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/organize_your_azure_resources_with_management_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/organize_your_azure_resources_with_management_groups/</guid>
      <description>Organize Your Azure Resources with Management Groups If your organization has many Azure subscriptions, you may need a way to efficiently manage access, policies, and compliance across those subscriptions. Azure management groups provide a governance scope above subscriptions, allowing you to organize your subscriptions into a hierarchical structure for unified policy and access management.
Hierarchy of Management Groups and Subscriptions You can build a flexible hierarchy of management groups and subscriptions to organize your Azure resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Azure for Free</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_azure_for_free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_azure_for_free/</guid>
      <description>Get Started with Azure for Free If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to explore the power of the cloud, Microsoft Azure offers an excellent starting point with its free account program. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of creating your Azure free account and taking advantage of the benefits it provides.
Key Features of the Azure Free Account   $200 Azure Credit: When you sign up for an Azure free account, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive a $200 credit to use towards any Azure services within the first 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud- Exploring Public, Private and Hybrid Cloud Models</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_exploring_public_private_and_hybrid_cloud_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_exploring_public_private_and_hybrid_cloud_models/</guid>
      <description>As the cloud computing landscape continues to evolve, organizations are faced with a critical decision - which cloud deployment model best suits their unique needs? The choice between public, private, and hybrid cloud can have a significant impact on factors like data security, scalability, cost, and control.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the pros and cons of each cloud deployment model, empowering you to make an informed decision that aligns with your business objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seamless Migration of Azure Cloud Services (classic) to Cloud Services (extended support)</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/seamless_migration_of_azure_cloud_services_classic_to_cloud_services_extended_support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/seamless_migration_of_azure_cloud_services_classic_to_cloud_services_extended_support/</guid>
      <description>Azure Cloud Services is a widely used Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) offering that allows developers to focus on building applications without having to manage the underlying infrastructure. Over the years, Microsoft has evolved its cloud platform, introducing new capabilities and deployment models to better serve the evolving needs of customers.
One such evolution is the introduction of Azure Cloud Services (extended support), which provides several benefits over the classic deployment model. Cloud Services (extended support) offers regional resiliency, feature parity with the classic model, and integration with Azure Resource Manager (ARM) capabilities like role-based access control (RBAC), tags, and policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure VM Maintenance with Maintenance Configurations and the Azure CLI</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_vm_maintenance_with_maintenance_configurations_and_the_azure_cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_vm_maintenance_with_maintenance_configurations_and_the_azure_cli/</guid>
      <description>Maintaining a fleet of Azure virtual machines (VMs) can be a complex task, but with the Maintenance Configurations feature and the Azure CLI, you can take control of when platform updates are applied to your resources. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the ins and outs of using Maintenance Configurations to optimize your VM maintenance strategy.
Creating Maintenance Configurations The first step in managing your VM maintenance is to create a maintenance configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Slack to Microsoft Teams- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_from_slack_to_microsoft_teams_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_from_slack_to_microsoft_teams_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Migrating from Slack to Microsoft Teams can be a complex and daunting task, but with the right plan and strategy, it can be a smooth and successful transition. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the entire process, from assessing your Slack workspaces to rolling out Teams in your organization.
Plan Your Migration from Slack Understand Your Slack Service Plan Your Slack service plan will determine what you can and can&amp;rsquo;t migrate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Guest Access in Microsoft 365 Groups</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_guest_access_in_microsoft_365_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_guest_access_in_microsoft_365_groups/</guid>
      <description>Collaboration and information sharing are essential in today&amp;rsquo;s dynamic work environment, and Microsoft 365 groups provide a powerful platform to facilitate these interactions. However, managing guest access to your organization&amp;rsquo;s groups can be a critical consideration, balancing the need for seamless collaboration with the imperative to maintain data security and compliance.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the best practices for managing guest access in Microsoft 365 groups, empowering you to harness the full potential of this collaborative tool while upholding your organization&amp;rsquo;s security posture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Homebrew- Your Comprehensive Guide to the Missing Package Manager for macOS</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_homebrew_your_comprehensive_guide_to_the_missing_package_manager_for_macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_homebrew_your_comprehensive_guide_to_the_missing_package_manager_for_macos/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Homebrew: Your Comprehensive Guide to the Missing Package Manager for macOS Homebrew is a powerful and versatile package manager that has become an essential tool for macOS users. It simplifies the installation and management of various applications, libraries, and utilities that are not provided by Apple out-of-the-box. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer, system administrator, or a power user, Homebrew can greatly improve your workflow and productivity.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the world of Homebrew, exploring its features, benefits, and practical applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Microsoft Teams with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_teams_with_powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_teams_with_powershell/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Teams is a powerful collaboration tool that can greatly enhance productivity and communication within an organization. One of the most effective ways to manage and customize Teams is through the use of PowerShell, a powerful scripting language that allows administrators to automate a wide range of tasks.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various ways you can use PowerShell to manage Microsoft Teams, from creating and managing teams and channels to configuring policies and settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building PowerShell on macOS</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_macos/</guid>
      <description>Building PowerShell on macOS can be a straightforward process, but there are a few important considerations to keep in mind. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the necessary steps to set up your development environment and successfully build PowerShell on your macOS machine.
Environment Setup To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to install either Homebrew or MacPorts - the two most popular package managers for macOS. These tools will help you install the required dependencies for building PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Guide to Azure Identity Management Security Features</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_azure_identity_management_security_features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_azure_identity_management_security_features/</guid>
      <description>Identity management is a critical component of any modern IT infrastructure, and Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure platform offers a robust set of tools and capabilities to help organizations effectively manage identities and secure access to resources. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the core Azure security features that empower identity management, including single sign-on, reverse proxy, multifactor authentication, Azure role-based access control (RBAC), security monitoring and reporting, and more.
Single Sign-On (SSO) Single sign-on (SSO) is a fundamental feature of Azure&amp;rsquo;s identity management offerings, allowing users to access all the applications and resources they need by signing in only once with their primary organizational account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enhance Your PowerShell Development with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/enhance_your_powershell_development_with_visual_studio_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/enhance_your_powershell_development_with_visual_studio_code/</guid>
      <description>Visual Studio Code (VS Code) has become a popular integrated development environment (IDE) for PowerShell developers, offering a rich set of features and capabilities that streamline the PowerShell development process. The PowerShell extension for VS Code, maintained by the PowerShell team and the community, provides an exceptional experience for writing, debugging, and managing PowerShell scripts.
Powerful Features for PowerShell Developers The PowerShell extension for VS Code delivers a wide range of features that enhance the PowerShell development experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing PowerShell on Linux- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell is a powerful and versatile tool that can be installed on a variety of Linux distributions, each with its own package manager and installation process. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the supported Linux distributions and the steps to install PowerShell on each of them.
Supported Linux Distributions PowerShell can be installed on several different Linux distributions, including:
Alpine Alpine is a lightweight and secure Linux distribution that uses the APK package manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrating ARM Templates with Azure Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/integrating_arm_templates_with_azure_pipelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/integrating_arm_templates_with_azure_pipelines/</guid>
      <description>Integrating ARM Templates with Azure Pipelines You can integrate Azure Resource Manager templates (ARM templates) with Azure Pipelines for continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD). In this article, you will learn two more advanced ways to deploy templates with Azure Pipelines.
Select Your Option Before proceeding, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the different options for deploying an ARM template from a pipeline:
  Use ARM Template Deployment Task: This is the easiest option when you want to deploy a template directly from a repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Securing Container Images in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/best_practices_for_securing_container_images_in_azure_kubernetes_service_aks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/best_practices_for_securing_container_images_in_azure_kubernetes_service_aks/</guid>
      <description>As container-based workloads become increasingly prevalent, ensuring the security of container images is crucial to avoid introducing vulnerabilities into your deployments. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the best practices for managing and securing container images in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS).
Secure the Images and Runtime Best Practice Guidance:
 Scan your container images for vulnerabilities. Only deploy validated images. Regularly update the base images and application runtime. Redeploy workloads in the AKS cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Microsoft Teams PowerShell Module- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_the_microsoft_teams_powershell_module_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_the_microsoft_teams_powershell_module_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering the Microsoft Teams PowerShell Module: A Comprehensive Guide Microsoft Teams is a powerful collaboration platform that has become essential for many organizations. To fully harness the capabilities of Teams, administrators and IT professionals can leverage the Microsoft Teams PowerShell module. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of installing, configuring, and utilizing the Microsoft Teams PowerShell module to manage your Teams environment effectively.
Requirements Before getting started, ensure that your system meets the following requirements:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>string</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/string/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/string/</guid>
      <description>string</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create and Manage Exported Data from Azure Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_and_manage_exported_data_from_azure_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_and_manage_exported_data_from_azure_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>If you read the Cost Analysis tutorial, then you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with manually downloading your Cost Management data. However, you can create a recurring task that automatically exports your Cost Management data to Azure storage on a daily, weekly, or monthly basis. Exported data is in CSV format and it contains all the information that Cost Management collects. You can then use the exported data in Azure storage with external systems and combine it with your own custom data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Visual Studio Code- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_visual_studio_code_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_visual_studio_code_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with Visual Studio Code: A Comprehensive Guide Getting up and running with Visual Studio Code is quick and easy. As a free, cross-platform code editor, VS Code can be installed in a matter of minutes, allowing you to start coding right away.
Cross-platform Availability Visual Studio Code is available for Windows, macOS, and Linux operating systems, making it a versatile choice for developers across different platforms. Regardless of your system, you can install VS Code and take advantage of its powerful features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Machine Learning Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_machine_learning_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_machine_learning_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Efficiently Manage and Optimize Costs for Your Azure Machine Learning Workloads
As you embark on your Azure Machine Learning journey, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to have a solid understanding of the cost management strategies and best practices to ensure your machine learning initiatives are both impactful and cost-effective. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the various aspects of planning, monitoring, and optimizing costs for your Azure Machine Learning resources.
Estimating Costs Before Getting Started Before you create any resources in your Azure Machine Learning workspace, it&amp;rsquo;s important to estimate the potential costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your Windows Server Licenses and Save on Azure Kubernetes Service</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_windows_server_licenses_and_save_on_azure_kubernetes_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_windows_server_licenses_and_save_on_azure_kubernetes_service/</guid>
      <description>Maximizing Your Windows Server Licenses on Azure Kubernetes Service Are you running Windows-based workloads in the cloud? If so, you may be able to save a significant amount on your Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) costs by taking advantage of the Azure Hybrid Benefit program.
Azure Hybrid Benefit is a licensing program that allows you to use your existing on-premises Windows Server licenses on Azure virtual machines, including those running in AKS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting to Microsoft Teams with PowerShell- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/connecting_to_microsoft_teams_with_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/connecting_to_microsoft_teams_with_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Teams is a powerful collaboration tool that has become essential for many organizations. The Connect-MicrosoftTeams cmdlet in the MicrosoftTeams PowerShell module allows you to connect to your Microsoft Teams environment and perform various administrative tasks. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the different ways you can authenticate and connect to Microsoft Teams using this cmdlet.
Connecting with User Credentials The most straightforward way to connect to Microsoft Teams is by providing your user credentials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting a Malicious PowerShell Script- A Detailed Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/dissecting_a_malicious_powershell_script_a_detailed_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/dissecting_a_malicious_powershell_script_a_detailed_analysis/</guid>
      <description>Dissecting a Malicious PowerShell Script: A Detailed Analysis Introduction You&amp;rsquo;ve stumbled upon a puzzling Base64-encoded PowerShell script that appears to have malicious intent. As a cybersecurity professional, your mission is to dive deep into this script, uncover its true nature, and reveal the potential risks it poses to our digital realm. Get ready to embark on a daring quest to safeguard our systems!
Decoding the Script The first step is to decode the Base64-encoded script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Azure DevOps Services- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_to_azure_devops_services_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_to_azure_devops_services_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Migrating to Azure DevOps Services: A Comprehensive Guide Moving your on-premises Azure DevOps Server to the cloud-based Azure DevOps Services is a strategic decision that can unlock a world of benefits for your organization. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the entire migration process, from understanding the basics to completing the post-migration tasks.
Understanding the Migration Process Before embarking on your migration journey, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to familiarize yourself with the key concepts and considerations involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Optimizing Virtual Machine Costs in Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/best_practices_for_optimizing_virtual_machine_costs_in_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/best_practices_for_optimizing_virtual_machine_costs_in_azure/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Virtual Machine Costs in Azure: Best Practices As organizations continue to embrace the cloud, managing and reducing costs for virtual machines (VMs) has become a critical priority. This comprehensive guide delves into the best practices you can implement to optimize the costs of your Azure virtual machines.
Use the Azure VM Selector to Identify the Right VMs for Your Needs The first step in cost optimization is selecting the appropriate virtual machines for your workloads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Line-of-Business Applications to Azure with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_line-of-business_applications_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_line-of-business_applications_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Migrating Line-of-Business Applications to Azure with Azure Migrate In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the step-by-step process of assessing and migrating a multi-tier application from on-premises Hyper-V infrastructure to Azure. We&amp;rsquo;ll leverage various Azure tools and services throughout the migration journey, including Azure Migrate, Azure Site Recovery, Azure SQL Database, and the Azure Database Migration Service.
Abstract and Learning Objectives This hands-on lab will teach you how to assess and migrate a complex, multi-tier application from Hyper-V to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Microsoft 365 Groups with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_365_groups_with_powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_365_groups_with_powershell/</guid>
      <description>As an administrator, managing Microsoft 365 Groups can be a crucial task to ensure smooth collaboration and information sharing within your organization. PowerShell provides a powerful tool to streamline these management tasks, and this comprehensive guide will walk you through the essential steps.
Link to Your Microsoft 365 Groups Usage Guidelines When users create or edit a group in Outlook, you can provide them with a direct link to your organization&amp;rsquo;s usage guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Microsoft Teams with PowerShell- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/managing_microsoft_teams_with_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/managing_microsoft_teams_with_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Teams is a powerful collaboration platform that has become an essential tool for many organizations. As an administrator, managing Teams can be a complex task, but with the help of PowerShell, you can streamline and automate many of the management tasks. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various ways you can use PowerShell to manage your Microsoft Teams environment.
Creating and Managing Teams with PowerShell The Microsoft Teams PowerShell module provides a set of cmdlets for creating and managing Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your SQL Server and Windows Server Investments with Azure Hybrid Benefit</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_sql_server_and_windows_server_investments_with_azure_hybrid_benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_sql_server_and_windows_server_investments_with_azure_hybrid_benefit/</guid>
      <description>Azure Hybrid Benefit is a powerful cost-saving program from Microsoft that allows you to get more value from your existing Windows Server, SQL Server, and Linux software investments when migrating to the cloud. By applying your on-premises licenses to Azure, you can save up to 85% over standard pay-as-you-go rates and seamlessly extend your hybrid infrastructure.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how Azure Hybrid Benefit can benefit your organization:
1. Save Up to 85% on Azure Costs With Azure Hybrid Benefit, you can use your existing Windows Server and SQL Server licenses to run virtual machines in Azure at a substantially reduced rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for a Seamless Migration to Azure DevOps Services</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_for_a_seamless_migration_to_azure_devops_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_for_a_seamless_migration_to_azure_devops_services/</guid>
      <description>Before you embark on your migration journey from Azure DevOps Server to the cloud-hosted Azure DevOps Services, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to understand the key concepts and considerations to ensure a successful transition. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the essential steps to get started with the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool and navigate the intricacies of the migration process.
Understanding the Data Migration Process The migration from Azure DevOps Server to Azure DevOps Services is not a one-size-fits-all process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Integration Runtimes in Azure Data Factory and Synapse Analytics</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_integration_runtimes_in_azure_data_factory_and_synapse_analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_integration_runtimes_in_azure_data_factory_and_synapse_analytics/</guid>
      <description>The Integration Runtime (IR) is the backbone of Azure Data Factory and Azure Synapse Analytics, providing the compute infrastructure to enable a wide range of data integration capabilities across different network environments. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re moving data between cloud data stores, dispatching transformation activities, or natively executing SSIS packages, the IR is the critical component that makes it all possible.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the different types of integration runtimes available, their capabilities, network environment support, and how to determine which one to use for your specific data integration needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizing Your Azure Resources with Management Groups</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/organizing_your_azure_resources_with_management_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/organizing_your_azure_resources_with_management_groups/</guid>
      <description>Azure Management Groups are a powerful tool for organizing and managing your Azure resources. They allow you to create a hierarchical structure that can be used to apply consistent policies, access controls, and governance across multiple Azure subscriptions.
In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of creating a new management group using the Azure Portal. Management groups are containers that help you manage access, policy, and compliance across multiple Azure subscriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of Azure Migrate- Your Gateway to Seamless Cloud Transformation</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_azure_migrate_your_gateway_to_seamless_cloud_transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_azure_migrate_your_gateway_to_seamless_cloud_transformation/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Power of Azure Migrate: Your Gateway to Seamless Cloud Transformation Azure Migrate is a comprehensive service that simplifies and streamlines the migration, modernization, and optimization of your IT infrastructure for the cloud. This powerful platform provides a unified experience, a range of assessment and migration tools, and seamless integration with third-party solutions - empowering you to navigate your cloud journey with confidence.
A Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate lies a single, centralized portal where you can start, run, and track your entire migration to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building PowerShell on Linux- A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_linux_a_step-by-step_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_linux_a_step-by-step_guide/</guid>
      <description>Building PowerShell on Linux can be a daunting task, but with the right guidance, it&amp;rsquo;s a rewarding process that can deepen your understanding of the platform. This comprehensive guide will take you through the necessary steps to set up your environment, install the required toolchain, and build PowerShell from the ground up.
Setting Up Your Environment The first step is to ensure your environment is properly configured for building PowerShell on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of PowerShell Development with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_development_with_visual_studio_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_development_with_visual_studio_code/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Power of PowerShell Development with Visual Studio Code If you&amp;rsquo;re a PowerShell developer, Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is the ultimate tool to take your productivity to new heights. Developed by Microsoft, VS Code is a cross-platform, open-source code editor packed with features that make PowerShell script writing and debugging a breeze.
Get Started with VS Code and PowerShell To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to install both Visual Studio Code and the PowerShell extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Migrating to Azure DevOps Services</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_migrating_to_azure_devops_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_migrating_to_azure_devops_services/</guid>
      <description>Before you use the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool to migrate your database with high fidelity, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand some key concepts and considerations.
Included and Excluded Data Not all data gets migrated when moving from Azure DevOps Server to Azure DevOps Services. The migration process includes your team project collection, which contains work items, version control history, build definitions, and more. However, certain data is excluded, such as extensions, service hooks, load test data, pipeline agents/pools, and project server integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Costs for Azure Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_costs_for_azure_machine_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_costs_for_azure_machine_learning/</guid>
      <description>As you work with Azure Machine Learning, it&amp;rsquo;s important to carefully plan and manage your costs to ensure your projects stay on budget. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through several strategies and best practices to help you optimize your spending and get the most value from your Azure investment.
Estimate Costs Upfront Before you start deploying resources, use the Azure Pricing Calculator to estimate the potential costs. This tool allows you to build out your Azure Machine Learning workspace and other supporting services, and it will provide an estimate of the monthly charges you can expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Azure Container Instances- A Comprehensive Approach</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_a_comprehensive_approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_a_comprehensive_approach/</guid>
      <description>Securing Azure Container Instances: A Comprehensive Approach Containers have become an increasingly popular way to package and deploy applications, but they also come with unique security challenges. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key security considerations for running container workloads on Azure Container Instances (ACI) and provide practical recommendations to help you secure your container ecosystem.
Use a Private Container Registry Container images are the foundation of your container-based applications, so it&amp;rsquo;s critical to ensure their security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover, Assess, and Migrate to Azure with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/discover_assess_and_migrate_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/discover_assess_and_migrate_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that simplifies the process of migrating, modernizing, and optimizing your infrastructure, data, and applications for Azure. This comprehensive service provides a unified portal to streamline your entire cloud migration journey.
Unified Migration Platform Azure Migrate offers a centralized hub where you can start, run, and track your migration to Azure. It provides a range of assessment and migration tools, including Azure Migrate: Discovery and Assessment, and Migration and Modernization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the &#34;Great Debate&#34; in the PowerShell Community</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_great_debate_in_the_powershell_community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_great_debate_in_the_powershell_community/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the &amp;ldquo;Great Debate&amp;rdquo; in the PowerShell Community Introduction The PowerShell community has long been engaged in a series of debates around best practices, coding styles, and various aspects of PowerShell scripting. These discussions, collectively referred to as the &amp;ldquo;Great Debate</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of Microsoft 365 Groups- Collaboration Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/harnessing_the_power_of_microsoft_365_groups_collaboration_made_easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/harnessing_the_power_of_microsoft_365_groups_collaboration_made_easy/</guid>
      <description>Harnessing the Power of Microsoft 365 Groups: Collaboration Made Easy In the modern, fast-paced business world, effective collaboration is essential for driving innovation, productivity, and success. Microsoft 365 Groups is a powerful platform that enables seamless teamwork and communication across your organization. As an administrator, understanding how to leverage this tool can transform the way your teams work together.
What are Microsoft 365 Groups? Microsoft 365 Groups are collaborative workspaces that provide a centralized hub for teams to share resources, communicate, and accomplish their goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Your Cloud Adoption with the Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/accelerate_your_cloud_adoption_with_the_cloud_adoption_framework_for_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/accelerate_your_cloud_adoption_with_the_cloud_adoption_framework_for_azure/</guid>
      <description>The Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure is a comprehensive set of tools, templates, and assessments that can help you quickly implement technical changes and accelerate your cloud adoption journey. This framework covers various phases of the cloud adoption process, from strategy and planning to readiness, governance, migration, innovation, and management.
Strategy The Cloud Adoption Framework offers several resources to help you define and refine your cloud adoption strategy:
 Cloud Adoption Strategy Evaluator assessment: Assess your current cloud adoption strategy and get recommendations on building and advancing your cloud business case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Azure Cost Management for Partners</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_azure_cost_management_for_partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_azure_cost_management_for_partners/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with Azure Cost Management for Partners As a Microsoft partner, Azure Cost Management is a powerful tool that can help you effectively manage and monitor your customers&#39; cloud costs. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the key features and capabilities of Cost Management, and how you can leverage them to gain visibility, control, and optimization of your customers&#39; Azure spending.
Understanding Cost Management Scopes In Cost Management, there are two main types of scopes: billing scopes and Azure RBAC scopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create and Manage Budgets in Azure Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_and_manage_budgets_in_azure_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_and_manage_budgets_in_azure_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Creating and Managing Budgets in Azure Cost Management Budgets in Azure Cost Management help you plan for and manage your organizational spending on Azure services. They enable you to proactively monitor costs, set spending limits, and receive alerts when thresholds are exceeded. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of creating, configuring, and managing budgets in the Azure portal.
Prerequisites  Understand the different Azure account types and scopes that support budgets, including Azure RBAC, Enterprise Agreement, Individual, and Microsoft Customer Agreement scopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Benefits and Differences of Cloud Computing Models</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_benefits_and_differences_of_cloud_computing_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_benefits_and_differences_of_cloud_computing_models/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Cloud: Unlocking the Power of Public, Private, and Hybrid Models
In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, cloud computing has emerged as a game-changer, offering organizations a vast array of benefits and deployment options. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re new to the cloud or looking to deepen your understanding, this comprehensive guide will explore the key differences and advantages of public, private, and hybrid cloud models.
Understanding Cloud Concepts: High Availability, Scalability, and More</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powershell-SlackBot- Harnessing the Power of the Slack Real-Time Messaging API</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/powershell-slackbot_harnessing_the_power_of_the_slack_real-time_messaging_api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/powershell-slackbot_harnessing_the_power_of_the_slack_real-time_messaging_api/</guid>
      <description>Powershell-SlackBot: Harnessing the Power of the Slack Real-Time Messaging API This project is a PowerShell implementation of a Chat Bot for Slack that utilises the Slack Real Time Messaging (RTM) API. This code is intended to provide a simple framework for anyone that wants to write a Chat Bot for a single Slack Team that is able to respond to Channel and Direct Messages. It would also be simple to extend the code to permit the Bot to respond to any other events exposed via the RTM API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Microsoft Teams with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_microsoft_teams_with_powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_microsoft_teams_with_powershell/</guid>
      <description>Manage Microsoft Teams with PowerShell Managing Microsoft Teams can be a complex task, but with the help of PowerShell, you can streamline many of the administrative duties. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various ways you can leverage PowerShell to manage your Microsoft Teams environment effectively.
Creating and Managing Teams The Microsoft Teams PowerShell module provides a set of cmdlets for creating, managing, and maintaining your Teams. These cmdlets allow you to perform tasks such as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding a GUI to Batch File Scripts on Windows</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/adding_a_gui_to_batch_file_scripts_on_windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/adding_a_gui_to_batch_file_scripts_on_windows/</guid>
      <description>Adding a GUI to Batch File Scripts on Windows Batch files are a powerful tool for automating tasks on Windows, but they are often limited to command-line interfaces. However, you can enhance your batch file scripts by adding graphical user interface (GUI) elements, making them more user-friendly and visually appealing. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore various techniques for adding GUI elements to your Windows batch file scripts.
Getting Started with the Basics The key to integrating GUI elements in batch files is the use of PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering User and Group Management in Azure DevOps</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_user_and_group_management_in_azure_devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_user_and_group_management_in_azure_devops/</guid>
      <description>Azure DevOps provides a powerful and flexible security system that allows you to manage permissions and access for users and groups. By leveraging security groups, you can easily control who can access and perform various actions within your Azure DevOps organization and projects.
Understanding Security Groups in Azure DevOps Security groups are the foundation for managing permissions and access in Azure DevOps. You can use both default and custom security groups to set permissions at different levels, including project, collection, and object-level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unified Approach to Interpreting Model Predictions with SHAP</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unified_approach_to_interpreting_model_predictions_with_shap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unified_approach_to_interpreting_model_predictions_with_shap/</guid>
      <description>Unified Approach to Interpreting Model Predictions with SHAP In the era of complex and highly accurate machine learning models, a critical challenge has emerged - the tension between model accuracy and interpretability. While advanced models like ensemble methods and deep neural networks can achieve state-of-the-art performance on large, modern datasets, their inner workings often remain opaque, making it difficult for even experts to understand why they make certain predictions.
To address this issue, researchers Scott M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Collaboration with Microsoft 365 Groups</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_collaboration_with_microsoft_365_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_collaboration_with_microsoft_365_groups/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Collaboration with Microsoft 365 Groups Microsoft 365 Groups is a powerful collaboration tool that enables teams across your organization to work together more effectively. By creating a Microsoft 365 Group, you can provide a shared set of resources that team members can access and use to drive their projects forward.
What are Microsoft 365 Groups? Microsoft 365 Groups is the foundational membership service that powers collaboration across the Microsoft 365 suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing PowerShell on macOS- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Installing PowerShell on macOS: A Comprehensive Guide PowerShell is a powerful cross-platform automation and configuration management tool that has become an essential part of the modern IT landscape. If you&amp;rsquo;re a macOS user, you&amp;rsquo;ll be glad to know that you can easily install and use PowerShell on your system. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the various installation methods available and help you get started with PowerShell on your Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Active Directory Security Groups- An In-Depth Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_active_directory_security_groups_an_in-depth_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_active_directory_security_groups_an_in-depth_guide/</guid>
      <description>Active Directory is a powerful tool for managing user and computer accounts, as well as controlling access to resources within an organization. At the heart of this access control system are security groups, which provide an efficient way to assign permissions and user rights to collections of users, computers, and other groups.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the world of Active Directory security groups, exploring their functions, scopes, and the default groups that come pre-configured with Windows Server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build PowerShell on macOS- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/build_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/build_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Building PowerShell on macOS can be a straightforward process, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to follow the right steps and address any potential issues that may arise. This guide will walk you through the process of setting up your development environment, installing the necessary dependencies, and building PowerShell using the provided build module.
Environment Setup To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have either Homebrew or MacPorts installed on your macOS machine. These package managers will help you install the required dependencies for building PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Cloud Deployment Models- Public, Private, and Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</guid>
      <description>Cloud computing has become an essential part of modern IT infrastructure, offering organizations a range of deployment models to choose from based on their specific needs and requirements. In this comprehensive article, we will delve into the three primary cloud deployment models - public, private, and hybrid - examining their key characteristics, advantages, and disadvantages.
Public Cloud The public cloud is the most common deployment model, where an organization&amp;rsquo;s data and applications are hosted on the infrastructure of a cloud service provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure DevOps Data Migration- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_devops_data_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_devops_data_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure DevOps Data Migration: A Comprehensive Guide Before embarking on your Azure DevOps data migration journey, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the key concepts and considerations that will ensure a successful transition from your on-premises server to the cloud-based Azure DevOps Services.
Understanding the Migration Process The Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool facilitates a high-fidelity migration, ensuring that the majority of your data is seamlessly transferred to the cloud. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to note that not all data is migrated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud- Public, Private, and Hybrid Deployment Models</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_public_private_and_hybrid_deployment_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_public_private_and_hybrid_deployment_models/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving landscape of cloud computing, understanding the different deployment models is crucial for organizations seeking to leverage the power and flexibility of the cloud. The choice of deployment model can significantly impact factors like security, scalability, and maintenance, making it a critical decision for any business.
Public Cloud: The Go-To Solution The public cloud is the most common deployment model, offering a compelling value proposition for many organizations. By leveraging the infrastructure and resources of a cloud provider, businesses can avoid the hassle of managing and maintaining their own hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Serverless Computing on Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_on_microsoft_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_on_microsoft_azure/</guid>
      <description>Serverless computing is a revolutionary approach to application development that enables developers to build and run applications without having to manage any underlying infrastructure. This article provides an in-depth look at serverless computing on Microsoft Azure, covering the key concepts, benefits, and patterns of serverless applications.
What is Serverless Computing? Serverless computing allows developers to build and run applications and services without having to provision or manage any servers. The cloud service provider (in this case, Microsoft Azure) automatically provisions, scales, and manages the infrastructure required to run the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Group Policy Management with AGPM 4.0</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_group_policy_management_with_agpm_4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_group_policy_management_with_agpm_4.0/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Group Policy Management with AGPM 4.0 Microsoft Advanced Group Policy Management (AGPM) is a powerful tool that enhances the capabilities of the Group Policy Management Console (GPMC), providing advanced techniques for managing Group Policy Objects (GPOs) in enterprise environments. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the step-by-step process of installing, configuring, and utilizing AGPM 4.0 to streamline your Group Policy management.
AGPM Server and Client Installation Installing AGPM Server As a member of the Domain Admins group, you&amp;rsquo;ll first need to install the AGPM Server on a member server or domain controller that will host the AGPM Service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of PowerShell- Essential Scripting Style and Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_essential_scripting_style_and_best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_essential_scripting_style_and_best_practices/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving world of PowerShell, the art of writing efficient, maintainable, and readable code is paramount. This comprehensive guide delves into the essential scripting style and best practices that can elevate your PowerShell prowess to new heights.
PowerShell, as a powerful scripting language, has become an indispensable tool for system administrators, IT professionals, and automation enthusiasts. However, with great power comes great responsibility. Adopting a set of well-defined best practices can help you navigate the intricacies of PowerShell and ensure your code is not only effective but also easily understandable and reusable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell: A Comprehensive Guide PowerShell is a powerful and versatile scripting language that has become an essential tool for system administrators, developers, and IT professionals. This comprehensive guide will take you on a journey to explore the various features and capabilities of PowerShell, helping you become a proficient PowerShell user.
Basic Commands Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the fundamentals of PowerShell. PowerShell provides a set of built-in commands, known as Cmdlets, that are written in .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell- Automating User Management and Service Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_automating_user_management_and_service_monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_automating_user_management_and_service_monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As a PowerShell enthusiast, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to dive into the practical challenges presented in this PowerShell interview scenario. PowerShell is a powerful and versatile tool that can streamline various administrative tasks, and in this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to tackle the two key scenarios outlined in the provided content.
Scenario 1: Capitalizing User Names and Assigning Administrator Rights In this scenario, we have a CSV file containing a list of user names that are incorrectly capitalized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Costs with Recommendation-Driven Actions</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendation-driven_actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendation-driven_actions/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Azure Costs with Recommendation-Driven Actions Managing cloud costs effectively is a critical concern for organizations leveraging Azure services. This comprehensive guide takes you through the process of identifying and acting on cost optimization recommendations provided by Azure Advisor, helping you reduce your Azure spending.
Unlock Savings with Azure Advisor Recommendations Azure Advisor is a powerful tool that works in tandem with Azure Cost Management to provide tailored cost optimization recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring a Self-Hosted Integration Runtime for Azure Data Factory and Synapse Analytics</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/configuring_a_self-hosted_integration_runtime_for_azure_data_factory_and_synapse_analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/configuring_a_self-hosted_integration_runtime_for_azure_data_factory_and_synapse_analytics/</guid>
      <description>The integration runtime (IR) is the compute infrastructure that Azure Data Factory and Synapse pipelines use to provide data-integration capabilities across different network environments. A self-hosted integration runtime can run copy activities between a cloud data store and a data store in a private network, as well as dispatch transform activities against compute resources in an on-premises network or an Azure virtual network.
This comprehensive guide covers the key aspects of setting up and managing a self-hosted integration runtime:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Diverse Perspectives in PowerShell Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_diverse_perspectives_in_powershell_best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_diverse_perspectives_in_powershell_best_practices/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Diverse Perspectives in PowerShell Best Practices If you&amp;rsquo;ve spent any time exploring PowerShell code projects, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely noticed that the PowerShell community has a wide range of perspectives on what constitutes the &amp;lsquo;right&amp;rsquo; way to write PowerShell scripts and modules. This diversity of opinions can make it challenging to establish a clear set of best practices that everyone agrees on.
The introduction provided outlines some of the key factors that have contributed to this lack of consensus over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptive Practices for Deploying and Running Azure Databricks at Scale</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/prescriptive_practices_for_deploying_and_running_azure_databricks_at_scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/prescriptive_practices_for_deploying_and_running_azure_databricks_at_scale/</guid>
      <description>Planning, deploying, and running Azure Databricks (ADB) at scale requires one to make many architectural decisions. While each ADB deployment is unique to an organization&amp;rsquo;s needs, we have found that some patterns are common across most successful ADB projects. This guide summarizes these patterns into prescriptive and actionable best practices for Azure Databricks.
We follow a logical path of planning the infrastructure, provisioning the workspaces, developing Azure Databricks applications, and finally, running Azure Databricks in production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Cloud Deployment Models- Public, Private, and Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</guid>
      <description>The cloud has become an essential part of modern computing, offering businesses and organizations a range of deployment models to choose from. Each model comes with its own set of advantages and disadvantages, and the choice ultimately depends on factors such as budget, security requirements, scalability needs, and maintenance preferences.
Public Cloud The public cloud is the most common deployment model, where your data and applications are hosted on the infrastructure of a cloud service provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Kubernetes Costs on Azure- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_kubernetes_costs_on_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_kubernetes_costs_on_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Kubernetes Costs on Azure: A Comprehensive Guide Kubernetes has become a popular choice for organizations looking to deploy and manage their applications in the cloud. However, as with any cloud-based infrastructure, cost optimization is crucial to ensure that your Kubernetes environment is running efficiently and cost-effectively. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore various strategies and best practices to help you optimize the costs of your Kubernetes deployment on Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell- A Comprehensive Guide to Automating Your Environment</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide_to_automating_your_environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide_to_automating_your_environment/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to PowerShell PowerShell is a powerful scripting and automation tool that has become an essential part of the Microsoft ecosystem. It provides a rich set of commands, functions, and modules that allow you to automate a wide range of tasks, from managing system configurations to interacting with various web services and APIs. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the core features and capabilities of PowerShell, and dive into practical examples to help you streamline your workflow and boost your productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell Modules- A Comprehensive Guide to Creating Reusable Script Modules</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_modules_a_comprehensive_guide_to_creating_reusable_script_modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_modules_a_comprehensive_guide_to_creating_reusable_script_modules/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell Modules: A Comprehensive Guide to Creating Reusable Script Modules PowerShell is a powerful automation tool that allows you to streamline your daily tasks and improve your productivity. One of the key features of PowerShell is its modular design, which enables you to create and share reusable code snippets called script modules. In this comprehensive guide, we will explore the ins and outs of writing PowerShell script modules, helping you become a more efficient and effective PowerShell user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with PowerShell in Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_powershell_in_visual_studio_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_powershell_in_visual_studio_code/</guid>
      <description>Unleashing the Power of PowerShell in Visual Studio Code Visual Studio Code (VS Code) has become a popular code editor for PowerShell developers, offering a comprehensive set of features and tools to streamline your PowerShell workflow. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the power of PowerShell within the VS Code environment, covering everything from installation and setup to advanced features and best practices.
Installing the PowerShell Extension The first step in integrating PowerShell with VS Code is to install the official PowerShell extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing PowerShell Core on Ubuntu Linux</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_core_on_ubuntu_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_core_on_ubuntu_linux/</guid>
      <description>Installing PowerShell Core on Ubuntu Linux If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to get started with PowerShell on Linux, specifically Ubuntu, this guide has you covered. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through installing the necessary dependencies, setting up PowerShell Core, and configuring Visual Studio Code (VSCode) for editing PowerShell scripts.
Install Useful Tools Before we install PowerShell Core, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure we have some helpful tools in place. We&amp;rsquo;ll start by updating the package manager:
sudo apt-get -y update Next, let&amp;rsquo;s install a few key tools:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Group Policy Management with Advanced Group Policy Management (AGPM) 3.0</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_group_policy_management_with_advanced_group_policy_management_agpm_3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_group_policy_management_with_advanced_group_policy_management_agpm_3.0/</guid>
      <description>Advanced Group Policy Management (AGPM) is a powerful tool that enhances the capabilities of the Group Policy Management Console (GPMC), providing robust change control and management features for your Group Policy environment. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the step-by-step process of installing, configuring, and leveraging AGPM 3.0 to streamline your Group Policy management.
Installing and Configuring AGPM Step 1: Install AGPM Server To get started, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to install the AGPM Server on a member server or domain controller that will host the AGPM Service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell Scripts- A Comprehensive Guide to the Windows PowerShell ISE</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_scripts_a_comprehensive_guide_to_the_windows_powershell_ise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_scripts_a_comprehensive_guide_to_the_windows_powershell_ise/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our comprehensive guide on how to write and run scripts in the Windows PowerShell Integrated Scripting Environment (ISE). Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned PowerShell user or just starting out, this article will provide you with a deep understanding of the various features and functionalities of the PowerShell ISE.
Creating and Running Scripts The PowerShell ISE allows you to create, edit, and run Windows PowerShell scripts with ease. You can work with a variety of file types, including script files (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage Roles and Permissions in Microsoft Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_roles_and_permissions_in_microsoft_sentinel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_roles_and_permissions_in_microsoft_sentinel/</guid>
      <description>Roles and Permissions in Microsoft Sentinel Microsoft Sentinel uses Azure role-based access control (Azure RBAC) to provide built-in roles that can be assigned to users, groups, and services in Azure. This allows you to grant appropriate access to Microsoft Sentinel and control what users can see and do.
Microsoft Sentinel-Specific Roles The built-in Microsoft Sentinel roles and their allowed actions are:
 Microsoft Sentinel Reader: Can view data, incidents, workbooks, and other Microsoft Sentinel resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Your Hybrid Identity Environment with Microsoft Defender for Identity</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/protecting_your_hybrid_identity_environment_with_microsoft_defender_for_identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/protecting_your_hybrid_identity_environment_with_microsoft_defender_for_identity/</guid>
      <description>Protecting Your Hybrid Identity Environment with Microsoft Defender for Identity Microsoft Defender for Identity (MDI) is a powerful tool that plays a critical role in safeguarding your hybrid identity environment. As a component of the Microsoft 365 Defender suite, MDI gathers signals from on-premises Active Directory servers and uses these signals to protect your organization against hackers who attempt to leverage compromised accounts to move laterally across your on-premises workstations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoothly Migrate Your On-Premises Azure DevOps Server to the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/smoothly_migrate_your_on-premises_azure_devops_server_to_the_cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/smoothly_migrate_your_on-premises_azure_devops_server_to_the_cloud/</guid>
      <description>Before you use the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool to migrate your database with high fidelity, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the key concepts and considerations involved in the migration process.
Understand What Data Gets Migrated Not all data gets migrated during the process. Separate databases outside the collection, such as reporting and SharePoint data, do not get migrated. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what is and isn&amp;rsquo;t included:
Included Data
 Collection Mapping: Each collection in Azure DevOps Server corresponds to one database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provisioning an Azure-SSIS Integration Runtime via Azure Portal</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/provisioning_an_azure-ssis_integration_runtime_via_azure_portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/provisioning_an_azure-ssis_integration_runtime_via_azure_portal/</guid>
      <description>Azure-SSIS Integration Runtime is now generally available in Azure Synapse Analytics, allowing you to use it and the Execute SSIS Package activity in your Synapse pipelines. This article provides a comprehensive guide on how to create an Azure-SSIS integration runtime (IR) in Azure Data Factory (ADF) or Synapse Analytics via the Azure portal.
The Azure-SSIS IR supports running packages deployed into the SSIS catalog (SSISDB) hosted by Azure SQL Database server or Managed Instance (Project Deployment Model), as well as packages deployed into Azure Files (Package Deployment Model).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing and Managing the Microsoft Teams PowerShell Module</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_and_managing_the_microsoft_teams_powershell_module/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_and_managing_the_microsoft_teams_powershell_module/</guid>
      <description>Installing and Managing the Microsoft Teams PowerShell Module Overview The Microsoft Teams PowerShell module provides a powerful set of cmdlets and tools for managing various aspects of Microsoft Teams, including creating and configuring teams, managing users and permissions, and automating Teams-related tasks. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of installing the module, signing in, updating, and uninstalling it, as well as explore the next steps for managing Microsoft Teams using PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Container Images in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_container_images_in_azure_kubernetes_service_aks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_container_images_in_azure_kubernetes_service_aks/</guid>
      <description>Securing Container Images in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) Container and container image security is a critical priority when developing and running applications in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS). Outdated base images or unpatched application runtimes can introduce security risks and potential attack vectors. To minimize these risks, you can integrate and run scanning and remediation tools within your containers during the build and runtime phases. The earlier you can identify and address vulnerabilities or outdated base images, the more secure your application will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building PowerShell on Linux- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Building PowerShell on Linux: A Comprehensive Guide If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer looking to build PowerShell on Linux, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. This guide will walk you through the process step-by-step, ensuring you have a smooth and successful experience.
Setting Up the Environment The first step is to set up your development environment. This guide assumes you&amp;rsquo;re using Ubuntu 16.04 LTS, as that&amp;rsquo;s the distribution the PowerShell team primarily uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Savings and Efficiency with Microsoft Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_savings_and_efficiency_with_microsoft_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_savings_and_efficiency_with_microsoft_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Cost Management is a powerful suite of FinOps tools that help organizations like yours analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud costs. With Cost Management, you can gain visibility into your cloud spending, proactively manage your budget, and identify opportunities to optimize and streamline your cloud infrastructure.
One of the key features of Cost Management is its ability to help you organize and allocate your cloud costs. By leveraging tools like billing profiles, invoice sections, management groups, and resource tags, you can ensure that costs are accurately attributed to the right business units and projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Cost Savings with Azure Hybrid Benefit for Windows Server, SQL Server, and Linux Subscriptions</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_cost_savings_with_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_windows_server_sql_server_and_linux_subscriptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_cost_savings_with_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_windows_server_sql_server_and_linux_subscriptions/</guid>
      <description>Azure Hybrid Benefit is a powerful cost-saving offering from Microsoft that allows you to optimize your hybrid environment by leveraging your existing Windows Server, SQL Server licenses, and Linux subscriptions. By taking advantage of this benefit, you can save up to 85% over the standard pay-as-you-go rate when running your workloads on Azure.
One of the key features of Azure Hybrid Benefit is its flexibility. You can use it in the Azure SQL platform as a service (PaaS) environment, allowing you to seamlessly migrate and modernize your SQL Server databases to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powershell-SlackBot- A Comprehensive Guide to Building a Slack Bot with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/powershell-slackbot_a_comprehensive_guide_to_building_a_slack_bot_with_powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/powershell-slackbot_a_comprehensive_guide_to_building_a_slack_bot_with_powershell/</guid>
      <description>Powershell-SlackBot: A Comprehensive Guide to Building a Slack Bot with PowerShell This project is a PowerShell implementation of a Chat Bot for Slack that utilises the Slack Real Time Messaging (RTM) API. This code is intended to provide a simple framework for anyone that wants to write a Chat Bot for a single Slack Team that is able to respond to Channel and Direct Messages. It would also be simple to extend the code to permit the Bot to respond to any other events exposed via the RTM API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Power of PowerShell on Linux- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unleashing_the_power_of_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unleashing_the_power_of_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell, the powerful command-line tool developed by Microsoft, has gained widespread adoption across various operating systems, including Linux. If you&amp;rsquo;re a Linux user looking to harness the capabilities of PowerShell, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the supported Linux distributions, installation methods, and community support options to help you seamlessly integrate PowerShell into your Linux workflow.
Supported Linux Distributions PowerShell can be installed on a variety of Linux distributions, each with its own package manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Guide to Installing PowerShell on Linux</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_installing_powershell_on_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_installing_powershell_on_linux/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive Guide to Installing PowerShell on Linux PowerShell is a powerful and versatile scripting language and automation tool that runs on a variety of platforms, including Linux. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the different methods you can use to install PowerShell on your Linux distribution.
Snap Package One of the easiest ways to install PowerShell on Linux is through the Snap package manager. Snaps are self-contained application packages that are easy to install, secure, and cross-platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Microsoft 365 Groups- Add, Remove, and Assign Owners</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/managing_microsoft_365_groups_add_remove_and_assign_owners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/managing_microsoft_365_groups_add_remove_and_assign_owners/</guid>
      <description>Managing Microsoft 365 Groups: Add, Remove, and Assign Owners In the modern workplace, collaboration is key, and Microsoft 365 Groups are an essential tool for bringing teams together. As an administrator, you have the ability to manage group membership and ownership, ensuring your organization&amp;rsquo;s groups are set up for success.
Adding Members to a Group Adding members to a Microsoft 365 Group is a straightforward process. As an admin, you can access the administrative center and navigate to the Active Groups page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell on macOS- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_on_macos_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s powerful and versatile scripting language, has become an essential tool for administrators and developers working on the macOS platform. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned PowerShell enthusiast or new to the technology, this comprehensive guide will walk you through the steps to install, configure, and utilize PowerShell on your macOS system.
Supported Versions and System Requirements Before we dive into the installation process, it&amp;rsquo;s important to ensure your macOS system meets the necessary requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud Deployment Landscape- Public, Private, and Hybrid Strategies</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_deployment_landscape_public_private_and_hybrid_strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_deployment_landscape_public_private_and_hybrid_strategies/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving world of cloud computing, understanding the different deployment models is crucial for organizations seeking to maximize their technology investments and meet their unique business requirements. The choice between public, private, and hybrid cloud models can have a significant impact on factors such as security, scalability, cost, and operational control.
Public Cloud: The Flexible and Cost-Effective Option The public cloud is the most common deployment model, where organizations leverage the infrastructure and services provided by cloud providers like Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services, or Google Cloud Platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell Scripting- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_scripting_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_scripting_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell Scripting: A Comprehensive Guide PowerShell is a powerful and versatile scripting language that has become an essential tool for IT professionals and administrators. This comprehensive guide will take you on a deep dive into the world of PowerShell scripting, covering everything from the basics to advanced techniques.
Input/Output and Objects PowerShell is built on the .NET Framework, which means that everything in PowerShell is an object. This object-oriented approach makes it easy to work with data and perform complex operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduling and Controlling Upgrades in Azure Kubernetes Service with Planned Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/scheduling_and_controlling_upgrades_in_azure_kubernetes_service_with_planned_maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/scheduling_and_controlling_upgrades_in_azure_kubernetes_service_with_planned_maintenance/</guid>
      <description>Scheduling and Controlling Upgrades in Azure Kubernetes Service with Planned Maintenance Maintaining and upgrading your Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) cluster can be a critical but complex task. Fortunately, AKS provides a powerful feature called Planned Maintenance that enables you to schedule and control cluster and node image upgrades. This article will guide you through the ins and outs of using Planned Maintenance to streamline your AKS cluster upgrades.
Understanding Planned Maintenance Your AKS cluster undergoes regular maintenance automatically, which can be divided into two types:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Microsoft 365 Groups with PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/managing_microsoft_365_groups_with_powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/managing_microsoft_365_groups_with_powershell/</guid>
      <description>As an IT administrator, managing Microsoft 365 Groups can be a crucial task to ensure your organization&amp;rsquo;s collaboration and communication channels are properly set up and secured. This comprehensive guide will walk you through various PowerShell cmdlets and techniques to effectively manage your Microsoft 365 Groups.
Link to Your Microsoft 365 Groups Usage Guidelines When users create or edit a group in Outlook, you can provide them with a link to your organization&amp;rsquo;s usage guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Azure DevOps Data Migration</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_azure_devops_data_migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_azure_devops_data_migration/</guid>
      <description>Get Started with Azure DevOps Data Migration Before you use the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool to migrate your database with high fidelity, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand some key concepts.
What Data Gets Migrated? Not all data gets migrated during the process. Separate databases outside the collection, such as reporting and SharePoint data, don&amp;rsquo;t get migrated. Here&amp;rsquo;s more detail on what does and doesn&amp;rsquo;t get migrated:
Included Data  Collection Mapping: Each collection in Azure DevOps Server corresponds to one database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell- Best Practices for Efficient and Maintainable Scripts</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_for_efficient_and_maintainable_scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_for_efficient_and_maintainable_scripts/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell: Best Practices for Efficient and Maintainable Scripts Navigating the Diverse PowerShell Landscape As you dive into the world of PowerShell scripting, you&amp;rsquo;ll quickly realize that the PowerShell community is a diverse and opinionated one. When scanning through code projects on the PoshCode repository or the Microsoft Learn Code Samples Gallery, you&amp;rsquo;ll encounter a wide range of approaches and perspectives on what constitutes &amp;ldquo;best practices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing On-Premises Machines for Migration to Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_on-premises_machines_for_migration_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_on-premises_machines_for_migration_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Preparing On-Premises Machines for Migration to Azure Azure Migrate is a service that helps you discover, assess, and migrate on-premises machines to Microsoft Azure. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the steps to prepare your on-premises machines before migrating them to Azure using the Azure Migrate service.
Verify Migration Limitations Before you begin, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the discovery, assessment, and migration limits for Azure Migrate. The table below summarizes these limits across different scenarios:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternate Ways to Install PowerShell on Linux</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/alternate_ways_to_install_powershell_on_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/alternate_ways_to_install_powershell_on_linux/</guid>
      <description>Alternate Ways to Install PowerShell on Linux Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s PowerShell is a powerful cross-platform automation tool that can be installed on various Linux distributions. In addition to the standard installation methods, there are several alternate ways to get PowerShell up and running on your Linux system.
Snap Package One of the easiest ways to install PowerShell on Linux is through the use of Snap packages. Snap is a container-based packaging format that makes it simple to install and maintain applications across a wide range of Linux distributions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Debugging in Windows PowerShell ISE</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_debugging_in_windows_powershell_ise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_debugging_in_windows_powershell_ise/</guid>
      <description>Debugging scripts can be a critical task for any PowerShell user, and the Windows PowerShell Integrated Scripting Environment (ISE) provides a robust set of visual debugging features to make this process more efficient and effective.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various techniques and tools available within the Windows PowerShell ISE to help you debug your scripts with ease.
Managing Breakpoints At the heart of the debugging process in PowerShell ISE are breakpoints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell Best Practices- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell Best Practices: A Comprehensive Guide Introduction As a seasoned PowerShell practitioner, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the diverse perspectives and practices within the PowerShell community. From code projects on PoshCode to the Microsoft Learn Code Samples Gallery, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that PowerShell users have a wide range of opinions on what constitutes &amp;ldquo;right and wrong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Visual Studio Code Settings for Maximum Productivity</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/customizing_visual_studio_code_settings_for_maximum_productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/customizing_visual_studio_code_settings_for_maximum_productivity/</guid>
      <description>Customizing Visual Studio Code Settings for Maximum Productivity As a developer, your code editor is your most important tool. Visual Studio Code (VS Code) provides a wealth of customization options to help you optimize your workflow and boost your productivity. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various settings you can tweak to personalize your VS Code experience.
Navigating the Settings Editor To access the VS Code settings, go to File &amp;gt; Preferences &amp;gt; Settings (or Ctrl+, on Windows/Linux, Cmd+, on macOS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Journey with the Microsoft Cloud Adoption Framework</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_with_the_microsoft_cloud_adoption_framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_with_the_microsoft_cloud_adoption_framework/</guid>
      <description>As organizations increasingly embrace cloud computing, their journey towards cloud adoption becomes more complex. The introduction to the hybrid and multicloud scenario outlined in the provided content consolidates various technical and non-technical considerations required to prepare for this journey.
The key focus of this scenario is to enable two primary outcomes:
 Hybrid and Multicloud Adoption: Building, deploying, and/or migrating solutions that are portable, allowing for ease of movement between cloud platforms with minimum vendor lock-in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Your Environment for a Hybrid and Multicloud Future with Azure Arc</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_a_hybrid_and_multicloud_future_with_azure_arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_a_hybrid_and_multicloud_future_with_azure_arc/</guid>
      <description>The modern business landscape demands flexibility, scalability, and seamless integration across on-premises, edge, and multicloud environments. As organizations navigate this complex landscape, the Cloud Adoption Framework&amp;rsquo;s Ready methodology can be a powerful guide, helping you prepare your environment for a successful hybrid and multicloud strategy.
At the heart of this approach are Azure landing zones - the building blocks of any Azure cloud adoption environment. These landing zones account for crucial elements like scale, security governance, networking, identity, cost management, and monitoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Microsoft Cost Management- Optimize Your Cloud Spending</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_cost_management_optimize_your_cloud_spending/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_cost_management_optimize_your_cloud_spending/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Cost Management is a powerful suite of FinOps tools that empowers organizations to analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud costs. This comprehensive platform provides a centralized view of your cloud spending, enabling you to make data-driven decisions and achieve cost optimization at scale.
Understanding the Commerce Data Pipeline At the core of Cost Management is the Microsoft Commerce data pipeline, which processes and tracks all commercial transactions, from consumer to enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Azure IP Ranges and Service Tags for the Public Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_azure_ip_ranges_and_service_tags_for_the_public_cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_azure_ip_ranges_and_service_tags_for_the_public_cloud/</guid>
      <description>The file &amp;lsquo;ServiceTags_Public_20240708.json&amp;rsquo; contains important information about the IP address ranges and service tags for the Microsoft Azure Public Cloud. This comprehensive file is updated weekly and provides the following details:
IP Address Ranges
 This file includes the IP address ranges for the Azure Public Cloud as a whole, as well as for each individual Azure region within the Public Cloud. The IP address ranges are currently provided only for IPv4, but there are plans to add support for IPv6 in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Cost Management Alerts- Monitoring Usage and Spending with Precision</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_cost_management_alerts_monitoring_usage_and_spending_with_precision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_cost_management_alerts_monitoring_usage_and_spending_with_precision/</guid>
      <description>Effective cost management is crucial for organizations leveraging the power of Microsoft Azure. One of the key tools in the Cost Management arsenal is the ability to set up cost alerts, which can help you stay on top of your Azure usage and spending. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the different types of cost alerts, their capabilities, and how to leverage them to gain better control over your Azure costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Hybrid Benefit for Linux Virtual Machines</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_linux_virtual_machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_linux_virtual_machines/</guid>
      <description>Azure Hybrid Benefit (AHB) for Linux is a powerful feature that allows you to easily switch between pay-as-you-go (PAYG) and bring-your-own-subscription (BYOS) licensing models for your Linux virtual machines. With AHB, you can remove licensing costs by bringing your existing Red Hat and SUSE Linux subscriptions directly to Azure, or utilize a PAYG model where you pay for subscriptions as you use them.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the key concepts of PAYG and BYOS licensing, how to enable AHB on new and existing VMs, how to check the current licensing model of an AHB-enabled VM, and the step-by-step process for converting between PAYG and BYOS models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Azure Costs with the Cost Optimization Workbook</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_azure_costs_with_the_cost_optimization_workbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_azure_costs_with_the_cost_optimization_workbook/</guid>
      <description>The Azure Cost Optimization workbook is a powerful tool designed to help you understand and optimize your Azure costs. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the various features and capabilities of the workbook, equipping you with the knowledge to make informed decisions and drive cost savings in your Azure environment.
Overview The Azure Cost Optimization workbook serves as a centralized hub for some of the most commonly used cost optimization tools and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy to App Service using GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploy_to_app_service_using_github_actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploy_to_app_service_using_github_actions/</guid>
      <description>Get started with GitHub Actions to automate your workflow and deploy to Azure App Service from GitHub.
Prerequisites  An Azure account with an active subscription. Create an account for free. A GitHub account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, sign up for free.  Set up GitHub Actions deployment when creating the app GitHub Actions deployment is integrated into the default app creation wizard. You just need to set Continuous deployment to Enable in the Deployment tab, and configure the organization, repository, and branch you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernizing Mainframe Applications with Azure- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/modernizing_mainframe_applications_with_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/modernizing_mainframe_applications_with_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>As organizations strive to stay competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital landscape, many are considering migrating their traditional mainframe applications to the cloud. Azure, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s powerful cloud platform, offers a compelling alternative to the mainframe, providing hyperscale compute and storage in a highly available environment.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key strategies and considerations for making the switch from a mainframe platform to Azure.
MIPS vs. vCPUs: Mapping Mainframe Workloads to the Cloud One of the first challenges in a mainframe migration is determining the appropriate level of compute resources needed to run your workloads on Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Deployment Models- Navigating the Public, Private, and Hybrid Landscape</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/cloud_deployment_models_navigating_the_public_private_and_hybrid_landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/cloud_deployment_models_navigating_the_public_private_and_hybrid_landscape/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to cloud computing, the choice of deployment model can have a significant impact on your organization&amp;rsquo;s operations, security, and cost considerations. The content provided outlines the three primary cloud deployment models - public, private, and hybrid - and their respective advantages and disadvantages. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive deeper into each model and explore how you can determine the best fit for your needs.
Public Cloud The public cloud is the most common deployment model, where your data and applications are hosted on the infrastructure provided by a cloud service provider, such as Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services (AWS), or Google Cloud Platform (GCP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Journey- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>As organizations continue to embrace cloud computing, the path to cloud adoption is becoming increasingly complex. The hybrid and multicloud scenario, as outlined in the Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure, presents a strategic approach to navigating this evolving landscape.
This comprehensive guide aims to provide a deep dive into the key components and considerations required to successfully implement a hybrid and multicloud strategy.
Understanding the Hybrid and Multicloud Scenario The hybrid and multicloud scenario focuses on two primary objectives:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Cost Savings with Azure Hybrid Benefit for Your Windows Server, SQL Server, and Linux Workloads</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_cost_savings_with_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_your_windows_server_sql_server_and_linux_workloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_cost_savings_with_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_your_windows_server_sql_server_and_linux_workloads/</guid>
      <description>Azure Hybrid Benefit is a powerful cost-saving offering from Microsoft that allows you to optimize your hybrid environment by applying your existing Windows Server, SQL Server licenses, and Linux subscriptions. By leveraging this benefit, you can achieve significant savings of up to 85% over the standard pay-as-you-go rates.
One of the key advantages of the Azure Hybrid Benefit is its flexibility. You can use it in the Azure SQL platform as a service (PaaS) environment, allowing you to take advantage of the scalability and flexibility of the cloud while still utilizing your existing investments in SQL Server licenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Kubernetes on Azure- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_kubernetes_on_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_kubernetes_on_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Kubernetes on Azure: A Comprehensive Guide When running a production-ready Kubernetes environment on Azure, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to focus on cost optimization to ensure efficient resource utilization and minimize operational expenses (OPEX). This guide will walk you through various strategies and best practices to optimize your Kubernetes clusters on Azure, drawing insights from the provided content and our own expertise.
Cluster Autoscaler: Dynamically Scaling Nodes The cluster autoscaler (CA) is a powerful tool for managing the scaling of nodes in an AKS cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Product Backlog Forecasting in Azure Boards</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_product_backlog_forecasting_in_azure_boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_product_backlog_forecasting_in_azure_boards/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Product Backlog Forecasting in Azure Boards Teams use the forecast tool in Azure Boards to help with their sprint planning efforts. By plugging in a value for the team velocity, the forecast tool shows which items in the backlog can be completed within future sprints. Both tools are team-specific and rely on the team&amp;rsquo;s ability to estimate backlog items. Once your team has completed a sprint or two, they can use the team velocity to forecast how much of the backlog they can finish within the upcoming sprints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Containers Across Clouds with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_containers_across_clouds_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_containers_across_clouds_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is the cloud-native solution for securing your containers, whether they&amp;rsquo;re running in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS), Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE), or on-premises Kubernetes clusters using Azure Arc.
Defender for Containers provides a comprehensive set of security capabilities to protect your container-based applications, including:
Cloud Security Posture Management (CSPM):
 Assess and strengthen the security configuration of your cloud resources Manage compliance against critical industry and regulatory standards  Cloud Workload Protection (CWP):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN When you have critical applications and business processes relying on Azure resources, it&amp;rsquo;s important to monitor those resources for their availability and performance. This article will guide you through the monitoring data generated by Azure Virtual WAN and how to leverage Azure Monitor to gain visibility into your Virtual WAN deployment.
Prerequisites To follow along, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have an existing Virtual WAN deployment configured. If you need help with that, check out these guides:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Azure Containers with Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution that helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This includes Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images.
To get started with Defender for Containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a Microsoft Azure subscription. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you can sign up for a free Azure subscription. You&amp;rsquo;ll also need to enable Microsoft Defender for Cloud on your Azure subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Migrate Assessments- Best Practices for Maximizing Migration Success</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_migrate_assessments_best_practices_for_maximizing_migration_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_migrate_assessments_best_practices_for_maximizing_migration_success/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that simplifies the process of discovering, assessing, and migrating workloads to Microsoft Azure. The Azure Migrate Discovery and assessment tool is a crucial component that helps organizations evaluate their on-premises infrastructure and determine the best path forward for their cloud migration journey. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into the best practices for creating assessments using the Azure Migrate Discovery and assessment tool, ensuring you can make informed decisions and optimize your migration efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Containerized Applications with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_containerized_applications_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_containerized_applications_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This powerful platform provides a range of security capabilities to help you protect your Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images.
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers offers both agentless and sensor-based capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your containerized environment:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Cost of Implementing a RAG-based Contact Center Solution with Azure OpenAI and Azure AI Search</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/estimating_the_cost_of_implementing_a_rag-based_contact_center_solution_with_azure_openai_and_azure_ai_search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/estimating_the_cost_of_implementing_a_rag-based_contact_center_solution_with_azure_openai_and_azure_ai_search/</guid>
      <description>Effectively managing the costs associated with implementing a Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) based contact center solution is crucial for businesses looking to leverage the power of large language models and intelligent search capabilities. The Customer Friendly Azure OpenAI Cost Estimator for RAG-based Contact Center Agents Usecase is a Python script that empowers you to estimate the monthly cost of utilizing Azure OpenAI and Azure AI Search within this context.
This comprehensive tool provides several key functionalities to help you plan and budget for your RAG-based contact center solution:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating a Line-of-Business Application to Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_a_line-of-business_application_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_a_line-of-business_application_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Migrating a Line-of-Business Application to Azure Overview In this comprehensive guide, you will learn how to assess and migrate a multi-tier application from an on-premises Hyper-V environment to Microsoft Azure. You will leverage Azure Migrate as the central hub for executing the migration, along with a variety of accompanying tools to ensure a successful migration.
After completing this guide, you will have a thorough understanding of the role of Azure Migrate and related migration tools, as well as the steps required to successfully migrate an on-premises multi-tier application to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your Cloud Efficiency with Microsoft Azure Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_efficiency_with_microsoft_azure_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_efficiency_with_microsoft_azure_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the world of cloud computing can be a daunting task, especially when it comes to understanding and managing your cloud costs. That&amp;rsquo;s where Microsoft Azure Cost Management comes in - a powerful suite of FinOps tools designed to help organizations like yours analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud spending.
In this comprehensive post, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the ins and outs of Azure Cost Management, exploring how it can help you take control of your cloud costs and drive greater efficiency across your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Costs- Best Practices for Identifying and Eliminating Unused Resources</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_best_practices_for_identifying_and_eliminating_unused_resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_best_practices_for_identifying_and_eliminating_unused_resources/</guid>
      <description>As cloud computing continues to revolutionize the way businesses operate, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to keep a close eye on the costs associated with your Azure infrastructure. Inefficient resource utilization can quickly lead to ballooning expenses, eating into your bottom line. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore two key best practices for optimizing your Azure costs by identifying and eliminating unused or underutilized resources.
Identifying Low Utilization Virtual Machines One of the most common sources of wasted Azure spending is virtual machines that are running but not being fully utilized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Computing- Exploring the Benefits, Service Models, and Deployment Options</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_cloud_computing_exploring_the_benefits_service_models_and_deployment_options/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_cloud_computing_exploring_the_benefits_service_models_and_deployment_options/</guid>
      <description>Cloud computing has become an integral part of modern technology, transforming the way organizations and individuals approach computing resources. In this comprehensive article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key benefits and considerations of using cloud services, delve into the differences between Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS), Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS), and Software-as-a-Service (SaaS), and compare the public, private, and hybrid cloud deployment models.
The Benefits and Considerations of Cloud Computing Cloud computing offers a wide range of benefits that can significantly impact an organization&amp;rsquo;s operations and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafting a Tailored Azure Migration Plan with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/crafting_a_tailored_azure_migration_plan_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/crafting_a_tailored_azure_migration_plan_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Defining Your Cloud Migration Goals Before embarking on your cloud migration journey, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand and evaluate your motivation for moving to Azure. The Cloud Adoption Framework outlines several common triggers and outcomes that can inform your strategic migration goals:
   Business Event Migration Outcome     Datacenter exit Cost reduction   Merger, acquisition, or divestiture Reduction in vendor/technical complexity   Reduction in capital expenses Optimization of internal operations   End of support for mission-critical technologies Increase in business agility   Response to regulatory compliance changes Preparation for new technical capabilities   New data sovereignty requirements Scaling to meet market demands   Reduction in disruptions and IT stability improvements Scaling to meet geographic demands    Identifying your key motivations will help you define clear, strategic migration goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Migration Execution Guide- A Comprehensive Approach to Azure Migrations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_migration_execution_guide_a_comprehensive_approach_to_azure_migrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_migration_execution_guide_a_comprehensive_approach_to_azure_migrations/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Migration Execution Guide: A Comprehensive Approach to Azure Migrations The Microsoft Azure Migration Execution Guide is a comprehensive resource developed by a team of FastTrack for Azure Program Managers and Engineers, in collaboration with the Microsoft SMC team, the Azure Advanced Cloud Engineering team, and the Customer Success Unit. This guide provides prescriptive guidance for structuring and executing successful Azure migration projects.
Key Objectives of the Migration Execution Guide   Consistent, Well-Considered Guidance: The guide aims to provide migration execution guidance at the business, project, and technical levels, ensuring a cohesive and well-planned approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right Cloud Deployment Model for Your Business</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/choosing_the_right_cloud_deployment_model_for_your_business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/choosing_the_right_cloud_deployment_model_for_your_business/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to cloud computing, there are three primary deployment models to consider: public cloud, private cloud, and hybrid cloud. Each model has its own unique advantages and disadvantages, and the right choice will depend on your business&amp;rsquo;s specific needs, budget, and requirements.
Public Cloud The public cloud is the most common deployment model, where your data and applications are hosted on the infrastructure of a cloud service provider like Microsoft Azure or Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape- Strategies for Success</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_strategies_for_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_strategies_for_success/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape: Strategies for Success Microsoft Azure provides a comprehensive set of products and features to help organizations build and operate their technology solutions in the cloud. However, many businesses find themselves needing to leverage multiple private and public clouds to meet their specific business requirements. This article outlines Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s perspective on the important cloud computing concepts of hybrid and multicloud, and provides guidance on navigating the associated challenges and opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of Azure Virtual WAN- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_the_power_of_azure_virtual_wan_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_the_power_of_azure_virtual_wan_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Azure Virtual WAN is a powerful networking service that provides optimized and automated connectivity solutions for enterprises looking to connect their branch offices, remote users, and cloud resources. This comprehensive guide will dive deep into the features, capabilities, and best practices of Azure Virtual WAN, empowering you to unlock its full potential and transform your network infrastructure.
Understanding Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a fully managed, cloud-based networking service that simplifies the process of connecting branch offices, remote users, and cloud resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Bike Share Rental Demand with Automated Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/forecasting_bike_share_rental_demand_with_automated_machine_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/forecasting_bike_share_rental_demand_with_automated_machine_learning/</guid>
      <description>Forecasting Bike Share Rental Demand with Automated Machine Learning In this comprehensive tutorial, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to create a time-series forecasting model for bike share rental demand using Azure Machine Learning&amp;rsquo;s automated machine learning (AutoML) capabilities. The step-by-step guide takes you through the process without requiring any coding, making it accessible for non-coding data scientists.
Prerequisites To follow along, you&amp;rsquo;ll need:
 An Azure Machine Learning workspace. You can create one by following the Create workspace resources guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Physical Servers to Azure with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_physical_servers_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_physical_servers_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Migrating Physical Servers to Azure with Azure Migrate Overview Migrating on-premises physical servers to Azure can be a straightforward process when using the Azure Migrate service. Azure Migrate provides a comprehensive solution to discover, assess, and migrate your on-premises infrastructure to the cloud.
In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to migrate physical servers to Azure using the Azure Migrate and Modernize tools. This process is useful in various scenarios, including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Your Linux Workloads to Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_your_linux_workloads_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_your_linux_workloads_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Azure offers a proven and reliable platform for running your Linux workloads. With a rich ecosystem of supported Linux distributions, flexible licensing options, and robust security features, Azure is an excellent choice for migrating and modernizing your mission-critical Linux applications.
Migrate to Innovate Azure provides a seamless path for migrating your on-premises Linux workloads to the cloud. Using tools like Azure Migrate, you can assess your existing environment, plan your migration, and then execute the migration process with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure DevOps Services Pricing</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/azure_devops_services_pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/azure_devops_services_pricing/</guid>
      <description>Azure DevOps Services pricing helps you scale your DevOps capabilities while controlling your costs. With flexible pay-as-you-go options, you can grow your DevOps practice incrementally as your needs change.
Your Azure DevOps Services bill includes the following elements:
Azure Pipelines
 Flat rate for Microsoft-hosted parallel jobs and self-hosted parallel jobs No charge for the free tier  Azure Artifacts
 Tiered pricing based on total artifact storage  Azure Boards, Repos, Test Plans, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Virtual Hub Routing in Azure- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_virtual_hub_routing_in_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_virtual_hub_routing_in_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Virtual Hub Routing in Azure: A Comprehensive Guide In the dynamic world of cloud infrastructure, the ability to manage and configure routing within your virtual hubs is crucial for maintaining seamless connectivity and efficient data flow. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of configuring virtual hub routing using the Azure portal, helping you unlock the full potential of your Azure Virtual WAN network.
Understanding Virtual Hub Routing A virtual hub in Azure Virtual WAN can contain multiple gateways, such as site-to-site VPN, ExpressRoute, point-to-site, and Azure Firewall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Azure Machine Learning Costs- Strategies for Efficient Model Training and Deployment</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_azure_machine_learning_costs_strategies_for_efficient_model_training_and_deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_azure_machine_learning_costs_strategies_for_efficient_model_training_and_deployment/</guid>
      <description>Optimize Azure Machine Learning Costs: Strategies for Efficient Model Training and Deployment As the demand for machine learning continues to grow, it&amp;rsquo;s critical to manage and optimize the costs associated with training and deploying models on the cloud. Azure Machine Learning provides a powerful platform for building and deploying ML models, but effectively managing the costs can be a challenge. In this in-depth article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore a range of strategies and best practices to help you optimize your Azure Machine Learning costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Costs with Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Effectively managing and optimizing cloud costs is a crucial aspect of any successful Azure deployment. This comprehensive tutorial will guide you through the process of identifying and acting on cost optimization recommendations provided by Azure Advisor, helping you reduce your Azure expenditure.
Unlocking Cost Savings with Azure Advisor Azure Advisor, a powerful tool integrated with Cost Management, analyzes your resource utilization and identifies areas where you can optimize your spending. By reviewing the cost optimization recommendations, you can uncover opportunities to resize underutilized virtual machines, purchase Azure Savings Plans, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximizing Your SQL Server Investments with Azure Hybrid Benefit</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximizing_your_sql_server_investments_with_azure_hybrid_benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximizing_your_sql_server_investments_with_azure_hybrid_benefit/</guid>
      <description>Migrating and modernizing your SQL Server deployments can be a complex and costly endeavor, but Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure Hybrid Benefit offers a solution that can help you save significantly on your licensing costs while streamlining your hybrid environment.
Azure Hybrid Benefit is a cost-saving offering from Microsoft that allows you to apply your existing Windows Server, SQL Server, and Linux subscriptions to your cloud workloads, unlocking substantial savings. By leveraging this benefit, you can save up to 85% over the standard pay-as-you-go rates, making it a highly attractive option for organizations looking to optimize their IT investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickly Deploy Microsoft Defender for Identity Sensors on Active Directory and Other Key Servers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/quickly_deploy_microsoft_defender_for_identity_sensors_on_active_directory_and_other_key_servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/quickly_deploy_microsoft_defender_for_identity_sensors_on_active_directory_and_other_key_servers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Identity is a critical security solution that helps protect your organization against identity-based attacks. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the quick installation process to get your Defender for Identity sensors up and running on your Active Directory, Active Directory Federation Services (AD FS), and Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS) servers.
Prerequisites Before you begin the installation, it&amp;rsquo;s important to ensure you have the necessary prerequisites in place:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Line-of-Business Applications to Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_line-of-business_applications_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_line-of-business_applications_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Migrating Line-of-Business Applications to Azure In this comprehensive guide, we will walk through the process of assessing and migrating a multi-tier line-of-business application from an on-premises Hyper-V environment to Microsoft Azure. We will leverage a variety of Azure tools and services to ensure a successful migration, including Azure Migrate, Azure Database Migration Service, and Azure Site Recovery.
Abstract and Learning Objectives Throughout this guide, you will learn how to:
 Use Azure Migrate to assess the on-premises environment and create a migration plan Migrate the application database from on-premises SQL Server to Azure SQL Database Migrate the web and application tiers from on-premises Hyper-V VMs to Azure virtual machines Reconfigure the application to use the migrated database Perform post-migration steps to prepare the application for production  After completing this guide, you will understand the role of Azure Migrate and related migration tools, and how to use them to successfully migrate an on-premises multi-tier application to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Containerized Assets with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containerized_assets_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containerized_assets_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses four core domains of container security:
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers offers both agentless and sensor-based capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your containerized environment:
Agentless Capabilities:
 Agentless Discovery for Kubernetes: Provides zero-footprint, API-based discovery of your Kubernetes clusters, their configurations, and deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Budget with Resource Manager Templates in Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_a_budget_with_resource_manager_templates_in_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_a_budget_with_resource_manager_templates_in_azure/</guid>
      <description>ource=</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up AutoML for Time-Series Forecasting with SDK and CLI</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/set_up_automl_for_time-series_forecasting_with_sdk_and_cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/set_up_automl_for_time-series_forecasting_with_sdk_and_cli/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to set up Azure Machine Learning&amp;rsquo;s automated machine learning (AutoML) for time-series forecasting using the Azure Machine Learning Python SDK and CLI. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover everything from preparing your data to orchestrating the entire workflow, including training, inference, and model evaluation.
Prepare Your Data for Forecasting To start, your input data for AutoML forecasting must contain valid time series in tabular format. Each variable should have its own corresponding column in the data table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Path to Successful Cloud Migrations with the Migration Execution Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_the_path_to_successful_cloud_migrations_with_the_migration_execution_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_the_path_to_successful_cloud_migrations_with_the_migration_execution_guide/</guid>
      <description>The migration to the cloud is a critical step in a company&amp;rsquo;s digital transformation journey, but it can also be a complex and daunting process. That&amp;rsquo;s where the Migration Execution Guide (MEG) comes in - a comprehensive resource developed by the FastTrack for Azure team at Microsoft, in collaboration with experts from various engineering and customer success teams.
The MEG provides prescriptive guidance for structuring and executing a successful migration project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Deployment Models- Public, Private, and Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</guid>
      <description>Cloud computing has revolutionized the way we approach IT infrastructure and service delivery. When it comes to cloud deployment, organizations have three primary models to choose from: public cloud, private cloud, and hybrid cloud. Each of these models offers distinct advantages and disadvantages, and the choice ultimately depends on an organization&amp;rsquo;s specific needs, budget, security requirements, and long-term goals.
Public Cloud The public cloud is the most common deployment model, where organizations leverage the infrastructure and services provided by a cloud vendor, such as Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services (AWS), or Google Cloud Platform (GCP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Azure Migration- A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_azure_migration_a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_azure_migration_a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful service that simplifies the process of migrating, modernizing, and optimizing your infrastructure in the cloud. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to move your servers, databases, web apps, or virtual desktops to Azure, Azure Migrate provides a unified platform to streamline every step of your cloud journey.
A Simplified Migration Journey Azure Migrate offers a range of tools to help you assess, migrate, and modernize your on-premises resources. The service provides a single portal to start, run, and track your migration to Azure, ensuring a seamless and efficient experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Monitor Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_monitor_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_monitor_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Cost-Effective Monitoring with Azure Monitor Azure Monitor is a powerful tool that provides comprehensive observability into your applications, infrastructure, and network. However, with its varied pricing models and features, understanding and optimizing your Azure Monitor costs can be a challenge. In this in-depth guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the different components of Azure Monitor pricing, share strategies to analyze and manage your costs, and provide practical tips to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the most out of your Azure Monitor investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Azure Container Instances- Best Practices and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_azure_container_instances_best_practices_and_strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_azure_container_instances_best_practices_and_strategies/</guid>
      <description>Containerization has revolutionized the way we develop, deploy, and manage applications, but with this powerful technology comes a unique set of security challenges. As organizations embrace Azure Container Instances to run their containerized workloads, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to address these security concerns head-on.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the security considerations for Azure Container Instances, equipping you with the knowledge and strategies to safeguard your containerized environments.
Securing Container Images Use a Private Registry Publicly available container images may not always be secure, as they can contain vulnerabilities in their various software layers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Your FinOps Practice with Improved Azure Cost Management Exports</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</guid>
      <description>Azure&amp;rsquo;s Cost Management service has recently introduced an &amp;ldquo;Improved Exports&amp;rdquo; experience that aims to simplify and enhance the process of exporting cost and usage data for FinOps professionals. This new feature offers a range of improvements designed to help organizations better manage their cloud spending and optimize their cloud investments.
The Improved Exports experience provides several key benefits:
Expanded Dataset Support The enhanced exports feature now supports a wider range of datasets, including price sheets, reservation recommendations, reservation details, and reservation transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Responsible AI- Practical Guidance for Building Trustworthy and Transparent AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/embracing_responsible_ai_practical_guidance_for_building_trustworthy_and_transparent_ai_systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/embracing_responsible_ai_practical_guidance_for_building_trustworthy_and_transparent_ai_systems/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Responsible AI: The Microsoft Approach Microsoft Responsible AI is a comprehensive initiative aimed at empowering developers and organizations to build AI systems that are transparent, trustworthy, and accountable. Recognizing the immense potential and impact of AI, this initiative provides invaluable guidance and resources to ensure ethical and responsible development of AI solutions.
At the heart of Microsoft Responsible AI are a set of guiding principles that serve as a framework for creating AI systems that align with core values such as privacy, fairness, transparency, accountability, and safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seamless Migration of Azure Cloud Services (classic) to Azure Cloud Services (extended support)</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/seamless_migration_of_azure_cloud_services_classic_to_azure_cloud_services_extended_support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/seamless_migration_of_azure_cloud_services_classic_to_azure_cloud_services_extended_support/</guid>
      <description>Seamless Migration of Azure Cloud Services (classic) to Azure Cloud Services (extended support) Azure Cloud Services is a widely used Platform as a Service (PaaS) offering that allows you to build, deploy, and manage scalable and highly available web applications and APIs. Recently, Microsoft introduced Azure Cloud Services (extended support), which provides several enhancements over the classic Cloud Services model.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of migrating your existing Azure Cloud Services (classic) deployments to the newer Azure Cloud Services (extended support) platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage and Optimize Azure Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_and_optimize_azure_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_and_optimize_azure_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Manage and Optimize Azure Costs: A Comprehensive Guide When you sign up for Azure, it&amp;rsquo;s important to get a handle on your spending and proactively manage costs. This comprehensive guide will walk you through key strategies and tools to plan, monitor, and optimize your Azure expenditure.
Get Estimated Costs Before Adding Azure Services Before provisioning any Azure resources, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to estimate the potential costs. You can use the following tools to get accurate estimates:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Virtual Hub Routing in Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_virtual_hub_routing_in_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_virtual_hub_routing_in_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Virtual Hub Routing in Azure Virtual WAN The Azure Virtual WAN service provides a powerful and flexible routing solution for your hybrid and multi-cloud networks. At the heart of this solution is the virtual hub, which serves as the central point of connectivity and routing for your network. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to configure and manage virtual hub routing using the Azure portal, empowering you to optimize your network&amp;rsquo;s performance and connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building an Ethical AI Framework- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_an_ethical_ai_framework_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_an_ethical_ai_framework_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Building an Ethical AI Framework: A Comprehensive Guide As artificial intelligence (AI) becomes increasingly integrated into our lives, organizations are facing the complex challenge of ensuring their AI implementations are ethical, responsible, and aligned with their values. The AI Ethics Framework provided by www.ethicalby.design offers a comprehensive approach to navigating these critical considerations.
Key Principles of Ethical AI The framework outlines several core principles for organizations to consider when developing and implementing AI systems:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximizing Your Microsoft Cloud Investment- An In-Depth Look at Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximizing_your_microsoft_cloud_investment_an_in-depth_look_at_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximizing_your_microsoft_cloud_investment_an_in-depth_look_at_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Cost Management is a comprehensive suite of FinOps tools designed to help organizations analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud costs. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re managing a single subscription or multiple billing accounts, Cost Management provides the insights and control you need to make informed decisions and maximize the value of your cloud investment.
Understanding the Commerce Data Pipeline At the heart of Cost Management is the Microsoft Commerce data pipeline, which underpins all commercial transactions across Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Your Azure Virtual Machine Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_azure_virtual_machine_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_azure_virtual_machine_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Optimize Your Azure Virtual Machine Costs: A Comprehensive Guide Running virtual machines (VMs) in the cloud can be a powerful and flexible solution, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand and manage the costs associated with them. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to plan, monitor, and optimize the costs of your Azure virtual machines.
Estimate Costs Before Deployment Before you deploy any virtual machines, use the Azure pricing calculator to estimate the costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Docker Security- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_docker_security_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_docker_security_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Docker Security: A Comprehensive Guide Docker has revolutionized the way we build, package, and deploy applications, but with this power comes the responsibility of ensuring the security of your Docker-based ecosystem. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key security features and best practices that will help you secure your Docker environment from end to end.
Understand Docker Security Fundamentals Docker provides a range of security features and tools to help you protect your container-based applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing a Resilient SQL Server Hybrid Cloud Solution</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/implementing_a_resilient_sql_server_hybrid_cloud_solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/implementing_a_resilient_sql_server_hybrid_cloud_solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing a Resilient SQL Server Hybrid Cloud Solution Overview In this hands-on lab, you will build a disaster recovery site for an on-premises environment. You will enhance the existing database solution to support a hybrid cloud-based disaster recovery solution, implement an archiving strategy and a backup/restore strategy designed to protect data.
At the end of the lab, you will be better able to design and use availability sets, Managed Disks, SQL Server Always on Availability Groups, Stretch DB and SQL Server Managed Backup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Active Directory Environment with Microsoft Defender for Identity</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_active_directory_environment_with_microsoft_defender_for_identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_active_directory_environment_with_microsoft_defender_for_identity/</guid>
      <description>Protecting Your Organization Against Identity-Based Attacks As the digital landscape continues to evolve, protecting your organization&amp;rsquo;s identities has become more critical than ever. Cybercriminals are increasingly targeting identity-based vulnerabilities to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data and systems. This is where Microsoft Defender for Identity comes in  a powerful tool designed to safeguard your Active Directory environment against these identity-based attacks.
The Importance of Defender for Identity Sensors Microsoft Defender for Identity is a cloud-based security solution that leverages your on-premises Active Directory signals to identify, detect, and investigate advanced threats, compromised identities, and malicious insider actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Azure Containers with Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform protects Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images, ensuring the security and resilience of your containerized applications.
Enabling Defender for Containers To get started with Defender for Containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a few prerequisites:
 Azure Subscription: You&amp;rsquo;ll need an active Microsoft Azure subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Comprehensive Migration Plan with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_a_comprehensive_migration_plan_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/building_a_comprehensive_migration_plan_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Defining Your Cloud Migration Goals Before embarking on your cloud migration journey, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand and evaluate your motivations for moving to the cloud. The Cloud Adoption Framework outlines several common triggers and outcomes that can guide your strategic migration goals.
Some key business events that may drive your migration include datacenter exit, mergers and acquisitions, reducing capital expenses, addressing end-of-support for mission-critical technologies, responding to regulatory changes, or improving IT stability and scalability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Your Azure Spend with Azure Advisor&#39;s Cost-Saving Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_azure_spend_with_azure_advisors_cost-saving_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_azure_spend_with_azure_advisors_cost-saving_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Azure Costs with Azure Advisor Azure Advisor is a powerful tool that can help you identify and address opportunities to optimize your Azure infrastructure and reduce your overall cloud spend. By analyzing your resource utilization and making targeted recommendations, Advisor empowers you to make informed decisions that can lead to significant cost savings.
Identifying Underutilized Virtual Machines and Scale Sets One of Advisor&amp;rsquo;s key capabilities is its ability to detect underutilized virtual machines (VMs) and virtual machine scale sets (VMSS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud Adoption Framework- A Comprehensive Guide to Successful Azure Migrations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_successful_azure_migrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_successful_azure_migrations/</guid>
      <description>Migrating workloads to the cloud can be a complex and daunting task, but with the right approach and guidance, it can be a seamless and rewarding experience. The Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure provides a comprehensive methodology to help organizations navigate the migration process and ensure a successful transition to the cloud.
The framework outlines four key stages in the migration journey: Prepare, Assess, Deploy, and Release. Each stage is designed to address the unique challenges and considerations that arise throughout the migration process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Costs and Monitoring Spending for Microsoft Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_costs_and_monitoring_spending_for_microsoft_sentinel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_costs_and_monitoring_spending_for_microsoft_sentinel/</guid>
      <description>Effectively managing and monitoring costs is a crucial aspect of ensuring the long-term success and sustainability of your Microsoft Sentinel deployment. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various tools and techniques available to help you gain visibility into your spending, set budgets, and proactively control costs.
Understanding Your Costs As you use Azure resources with Microsoft Sentinel, you will inevitably incur costs. These costs can vary based on factors like time intervals (seconds, minutes, hours, days) and usage units (bytes, megabytes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cosmos DB Pricing- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cosmos_db_pricing_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cosmos_db_pricing_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the pricing landscape of Azure Cosmos DB can be a daunting task, but with the right information, you can optimize your costs and maximize the value of this powerful NoSQL database service. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the intricacies of Azure Cosmos DB&amp;rsquo;s pricing model, uncover strategies to save on your database operations, and explore the various options available for developers to get started with Azure Cosmos DB for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cost Management- Creating and Managing Budgets</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_management_creating_and_managing_budgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_management_creating_and_managing_budgets/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure Cost Management: Creating and Managing Budgets Budgets in Azure Cost Management are a powerful tool to help you plan, monitor, and control your cloud spending. By creating and managing budgets, you can proactively inform your organization about spending, manage costs, and track how spending evolves over time.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of creating and managing budgets in the Azure portal, as well as exploring programmatic options using PowerShell, CLI, and Terraform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Your Azure Costs with Advisor Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_your_azure_costs_with_advisor_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_your_azure_costs_with_advisor_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Azure Advisor is a powerful tool that can help you reduce your overall Azure spending by identifying idle and underutilized resources. By implementing the cost recommendations provided by Advisor, you can optimize your cloud costs and ensure your Azure resources are being used efficiently.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various cost-saving opportunities identified by Advisor and provide you with actionable steps to implement them.
AI Services Potential Cost Savings on AI Services Advisor has identified several of your AI service resources, such as Document Intelligence (formerly Form Recognizer), Computer Vision, Speech Service, Translator, LUIS, and Language Service, that could benefit from using a Commitment tier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud- Exploring Public, Private, and Hybrid Cloud Models</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_exploring_public_private_and_hybrid_cloud_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_exploring_public_private_and_hybrid_cloud_models/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving world of cloud computing, organizations face a crucial decision when it comes to their cloud deployment strategy. The choice between public, private, or hybrid cloud models can have a significant impact on factors such as security, scalability, and cost-effectiveness. Understanding the nuances of each deployment model is essential for making an informed decision that aligns with your business needs.
Public Cloud: The Scalable and Cost-Effective Option The public cloud has emerged as the most common deployment model, offering organizations a highly scalable and cost-effective solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Your Containerized Infrastructure with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive, cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets, including Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images, across multicloud and on-premises environments.
Four Core Domains of Container Security Defender for Containers assists you with four key areas of container security:
  Security Posture Management:
 Provides continuous monitoring of cloud and Kubernetes APIs to discover resources, offer comprehensive inventory capabilities, detect misconfigurations, and provide guidelines to mitigate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Azure Migrate- Your Pathway to Seamless Cloud Transformation</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_azure_migrate_your_pathway_to_seamless_cloud_transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_azure_migrate_your_pathway_to_seamless_cloud_transformation/</guid>
      <description>Navigating Azure Migrate: Your Pathway to Seamless Cloud Transformation Azure Migrate is a powerful service that simplifies the journey to the cloud, providing a comprehensive platform for migration, modernization, and optimization. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to migrate servers, databases, web apps, or virtual desktops, Azure Migrate offers a range of integrated tools to streamline the process.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate is a single, centralized portal that allows you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Migration Execution Guide- A Comprehensive Roadmap to Successful Cloud Transformation</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/azure_migration_execution_guide_a_comprehensive_roadmap_to_successful_cloud_transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/azure_migration_execution_guide_a_comprehensive_roadmap_to_successful_cloud_transformation/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migration Execution Guide: A Comprehensive Roadmap to Successful Cloud Transformation This comprehensive guide, developed by a team of FastTrack for Azure experts, provides prescriptive guidance for executing a successful migration project to Microsoft Azure. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re migrating your entire infrastructure, modernizing your applications, or expanding your cloud presence, this guide covers the essential steps and best practices to ensure a smooth and efficient transition.
Key Objectives   Consistent Guidance: The Migration Execution Guide (MEG) delivers well-considered guidance at the business, project, and technical levels to ensure a standardized approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplify Your Cloud Migration Journey with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/simplify_your_cloud_migration_journey_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/simplify_your_cloud_migration_journey_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Streamlining the Migration to Azure Azure Migrate provides a comprehensive solution to simplify your journey to the cloud. This powerful service offers a range of tools and capabilities to help you assess, migrate, and modernize your on-premises infrastructure, data, and applications.
Unified Migration Platform Azure Migrate acts as a single portal to start, run, and track your migration to Azure. It provides a seamless experience, allowing you to manage the entire migration process from a centralized location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Your Cloud Migration- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/accelerating_your_cloud_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/accelerating_your_cloud_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Accelerating Your Cloud Migration: A Comprehensive Guide Migrating to the cloud can be a daunting task, but with the right approach, you can significantly accelerate your migration efforts and realize business value faster. This comprehensive guide, based on the Microsoft Cloud Adoption Framework, outlines the key steps to help you overcome common migration roadblocks and streamline your cloud migration journey.
Step 1: Align Stakeholders Successful cloud migration starts with aligning your business and IT stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Continuous Integration and Delivery in Azure Data Factory</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_continuous_integration_and_delivery_in_azure_data_factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_continuous_integration_and_delivery_in_azure_data_factory/</guid>
      <description>Continuous Integration and Delivery in Azure Data Factory Continuous integration is the practice of automatically testing each change made to your codebase as early as possible. Continuous delivery then takes the tested changes and pushes them to a staging or production environment.
In Azure Data Factory, continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) refers to the process of moving your data pipelines from one environment (like development) to another (like test or production).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Azure Costs with Optimization Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/reduce_azure_costs_with_optimization_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/reduce_azure_costs_with_optimization_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing your Azure costs can have a significant impact on your overall cloud spending. This comprehensive guide walks you through leveraging Azure Advisor recommendations to identify and address underutilized resources, ultimately helping you reduce your Azure costs.
Understand Cost Optimization Recommendations Azure Advisor, integrated with Cost Management, provides valuable recommendations to help you optimize your Azure resource utilization and costs. These recommendations identify usage inefficiencies and potential savings opportunities.
The recommendations are categorized by their potential impact:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Integration and Delivery in Azure Data Factory</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/continuous_integration_and_delivery_in_azure_data_factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/continuous_integration_and_delivery_in_azure_data_factory/</guid>
      <description>Continuous integration is the practice of testing each change made to your codebase automatically and as early as possible. Continuous delivery follows the testing that happens during continuous integration and pushes changes to a staging or production system.
In Azure Data Factory, continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) means moving Data Factory pipelines from one environment (development, test, production) to another. Azure Data Factory utilizes Azure Resource Manager templates to store the configuration of your various ADF entities (pipelines, datasets, data flows, and so on).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamline Your Data Migration to Azure Storage with AzCopy</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamline_your_data_migration_to_azure_storage_with_azcopy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamline_your_data_migration_to_azure_storage_with_azcopy/</guid>
      <description>Streamline Your Data Migration to Azure Storage with AzCopy Are you looking to move your on-premises data to the cloud? Azure Storage&amp;rsquo;s AzCopy tool can make the process quick and efficient. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to seamlessly migrate your data to Azure Storage using AzCopy.
What is AzCopy? AzCopy is a powerful command-line tool that allows you to copy data to and from Azure Blob storage, Azure Files, and Azure Table storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Security with Microsoft Defender for Cloud- Improve Your Secure Posture</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_cloud_improve_your_secure_posture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_cloud_improve_your_secure_posture/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure Security with Microsoft Defender for Cloud: Improve Your Secure Posture In this comprehensive article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how you can leverage the powerful features of Microsoft Defender for Cloud to enhance the security posture of your Azure environment. By the end of this post, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a deep understanding of how to use vulnerability assessment for virtual machines and containers, automate recommendation workflows, and access your secure score data using Azure Resource Graph (ARG).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Cloud Adoption Framework- A Comprehensive Guide to Migrating Workloads to Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_migrating_workloads_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_cloud_adoption_framework_a_comprehensive_guide_to_migrating_workloads_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Migrating workloads to the cloud can be a complex and daunting task, but with the right framework and guidance, it can be a seamless and successful experience. The Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure provides a comprehensive and proven methodology to help organizations plan, prepare, and execute their cloud migration journey.
In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the key stages of the migration process and explore how the Cloud Adoption Framework can help you navigate each step with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Black Box- Interpreting Machine Learning Models with Azure Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_the_black_box_interpreting_machine_learning_models_with_azure_machine_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_the_black_box_interpreting_machine_learning_models_with_azure_machine_learning/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the Black Box: Interpreting Machine Learning Models with Azure Machine Learning In the world of machine learning, models can often become akin to black boxes - powerful predictive tools that deliver remarkable results, yet their inner workings remain opaque and difficult to understand. This is where model interpretability comes into play, providing invaluable insights that can shape the development, deployment, and governance of your machine learning applications.
Azure Machine Learning offers a comprehensive suite of tools and techniques to help you unravel the mysteries of your models, empowering you to build more transparent, trustworthy, and responsible AI systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Container Security with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_container_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_container_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses four core domains of container security: security posture management, vulnerability assessment, runtime threat protection, and deployment and monitoring.
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides agentless capabilities that enable zero-footprint, API-based discovery of your Kubernetes clusters, their configurations, and deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Centrally Managed Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_centrally_managed_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_sql_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_centrally_managed_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_sql_server/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Centrally Managed Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of proactively managing and optimizing your use of Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server. By centrally managing this benefit, you can reduce the costs of running Azure SQL and ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the most value out of your existing SQL Server licenses.
Prerequisites Before you begin, make sure you have:
  Read and understood the What is centrally managed Azure Hybrid Benefit?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Different Cloud Deployment Models- Public, Private, and Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_different_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_the_different_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid/</guid>
      <description>In the rapidly evolving world of cloud computing, businesses and organizations face an important decision - which cloud deployment model best fits their needs? The choice can significantly impact the security, scalability, and maintenance of their data and applications. This comprehensive article delves into the three primary cloud deployment models: public, private, and hybrid, providing a detailed overview of their advantages, disadvantages, and real-world use cases.
Public Cloud: The Most Common Deployment Model The public cloud is the most widely adopted cloud deployment model, offering a highly scalable and cost-effective solution for businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate- Simplifying Your Cloud Migration Journey</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_migration_journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_migration_journey/</guid>
      <description>A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate: Simplifying Your Cloud Migration Journey Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that provides a simplified and streamlined approach to migrating, modernizing, and optimizing your infrastructure, data, and applications for the Azure cloud. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to migrate on-premises servers, databases, web apps, or virtual desktops, Azure Migrate offers a comprehensive suite of tools and services to make your cloud journey a success.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate is a single, unified portal that allows you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Guide to Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Microsoft Defender for Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses the unique security challenges associated with the rapid growth and adoption of containers and Kubernetes.
Defender for Containers provides a holistic approach to container security, focusing on four core domains:
  Security Posture Management: Continuously monitors cloud APIs, Kubernetes APIs, and Kubernetes workloads to discover resources, detect misconfigurations, provide risk assessment, and enable enhanced risk hunting capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cost Automation- Unlock the Power of Programmatic Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Maximizing the value of your cloud investment requires a strategic approach to cost management. Azure offers a robust set of automation tools and APIs that enable you to streamline your cost data retrieval, analysis, and alerting processes. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various techniques and best practices for automating your Azure cost management workflows.
Automate Cost Data Retrieval for Offline Analysis Integrating your Azure cost data with other datasets or internal systems can provide valuable insights to drive key business decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape- Maximize the Benefits, Minimize the Concerns</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_maximize_the_benefits_minimize_the_concerns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_maximize_the_benefits_minimize_the_concerns/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape: Maximize the Benefits, Minimize the Concerns As the digital landscape continues to evolve, more and more organizations are embracing the power of hybrid and multicloud environments. Microsoft Azure, as an enterprise-grade cloud provider, offers a comprehensive suite of products and features to help you build and operate your technology solutions across public, hybrid, and multicloud setups.
Defining Hybrid and Multicloud A hybrid cloud is a type of cloud computing that combines a private cloud (on-premises infrastructure) with a public cloud (computing services offered by third-party providers over the public internet).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gain Cost Visibility and Accountability with Azure Cost Allocation</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/gain_cost_visibility_and_accountability_with_azure_cost_allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/gain_cost_visibility_and_accountability_with_azure_cost_allocation/</guid>
      <description>As organizations increasingly rely on Azure to power their digital transformation, managing and understanding cloud costs becomes a critical priority. This is especially true for large enterprises that centrally manage Azure services or resources, while different internal departments or business units consume them. The centrally managing team often wants to reallocate the cost of the shared services back out to the internal departments or organizational business units who are actively using the services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Cloud Infrastructure- End-to-End Security in Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_cloud_infrastructure_end-to-end_security_in_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_cloud_infrastructure_end-to-end_security_in_azure/</guid>
      <description>Azure is a robust cloud platform that offers a comprehensive suite of security services to help businesses safeguard their cloud resources, detect threats, and respond effectively. In this in-depth article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various security capabilities available in Azure and how you can leverage them to create a secure, end-to-end cloud environment.
Secure and Protect One of the key advantages of using Azure is the wide array of security tools and capabilities it provides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of Azure Migration- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_azure_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlock_the_power_of_azure_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Power of Azure Migration: A Comprehensive Guide Introduction Migrating to the cloud can be a daunting task, but with the right guidance and tools, it can be a smooth and successful journey. The Migration Execution Guide, developed by a team of FastTrack for Azure experts, provides comprehensive and prescriptive guidance to help organizations navigate the complexities of Azure migration.
Key Objectives The Migration Execution Guide aims to:
 Provide Consistent Guidance: Offer well-considered migration execution guidance at the business, project, and technical levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize and Simplify Your Azure Migration Journey with CloudSphere</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_and_simplify_your_azure_migration_journey_with_cloudsphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_and_simplify_your_azure_migration_journey_with_cloudsphere/</guid>
      <description>As organizations look to migrate their workloads to the Azure cloud, they face a number of challenges. From discovering and assessing complex on-premises environments to ensuring a seamless and cost-effective migration process, the path to Azure can be daunting.
Fortunately, CloudSphere provides a comprehensive solution that simplifies and optimizes the entire Azure migration journey. Integrated directly with Azure Migrate, CloudSphere&amp;rsquo;s Discovery and Optimization Insights platform delivers unparalleled visibility, analysis, and recommendations to ensure your migration to Azure is a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid and Multicloud- Unlocking the Power of the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/hybrid_and_multicloud_unlocking_the_power_of_the_cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/hybrid_and_multicloud_unlocking_the_power_of_the_cloud/</guid>
      <description>Hybrid and Multicloud: Unlocking the Power of the Cloud As businesses strive to remain agile, innovative, and competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital landscape, the need for a flexible and scalable technology infrastructure has become paramount. Enter the world of hybrid and multicloud computing - a transformative approach that empowers organizations to harness the full potential of cloud technology while addressing the unique challenges they face.
Microsoft Azure, as a leading enterprise-grade cloud provider, understands the intricacies of this evolving landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Hybrid and Multicloud Computing for Mission-Critical Applications</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/the_power_of_hybrid_and_multicloud_computing_for_mission-critical_applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/the_power_of_hybrid_and_multicloud_computing_for_mission-critical_applications/</guid>
      <description>The Power of Hybrid and Multicloud Computing for Mission-Critical Applications As modern businesses strive to stay competitive and agile, the need for a flexible and scalable IT infrastructure has become increasingly crucial. This is where the power of hybrid and multicloud computing shines, offering organizations the ability to seamlessly blend on-premises resources with the vast capabilities of public cloud platforms.
Understanding Hybrid and Multicloud A hybrid cloud is a computing environment that combines a private cloud (on-premises infrastructure) with a public cloud (services provided by third-party providers over the internet).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demand Forecasting with Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/demand_forecasting_with_deep_learning_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/demand_forecasting_with_deep_learning_models/</guid>
      <description>In this notebook, we&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to use Azure Machine Learning&amp;rsquo;s automated machine learning (AutoML) for time-series forecasting, specifically using deep learning models to forecast GitHub daily active users (DAU).
Prepare Data We&amp;rsquo;ll start by loading the GitHub daily active users data into an MLTable, which is the required format for AutoML forecasting jobs.
import pandas as pd from azure.ai.ml import Input from azure.ai.ml.constants import AssetTypes # Load the GitHub DAU data df = pd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Azure Containers with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution designed to enhance the security of your containerized workloads across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your Kubernetes clusters, container registries, container images, and more.
Gain Visibility and Control Over Your Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers offers a range of powerful features to protect your containerized assets:
  Cloud Security Posture Management (CSPM): Defender for Containers provides both foundational and advanced CSPM capabilities, enabling you to continuously assess your security posture, receive security recommendations, and benchmark your cloud security against industry standards across Azure, AWS, and Google Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up a Simulated Hybrid Cloud Environment for Testing</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/setting_up_a_simulated_hybrid_cloud_environment_for_testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/setting_up_a_simulated_hybrid_cloud_environment_for_testing/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up a Simulated Hybrid Cloud Environment for Testing Microsoft Azure provides a flexible and scalable platform for creating test environments that simulate a hybrid cloud setup. This article walks you through the process of setting up a simulated hybrid cloud test environment using two separate Azure virtual networks and a VNet-to-VNet connection.
This setup simulates a hybrid cloud production environment consisting of:
 A simulated and simplified on-premises network hosted in an Azure virtual network (the TestLab virtual network).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Serverless Computing with Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_with_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_with_azure/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Serverless Computing with Azure Serverless computing is a cloud-based execution model that allows developers to build and run applications without having to manage the underlying infrastructure. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the world of serverless computing and explore how Azure enables you to leverage this powerful approach.
What is Serverless Computing? Serverless computing is a cloud computing execution model where the cloud provider (such as Azure) is responsible for executing a piece of code by dynamically allocating the required resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Microsoft Defender for Containers to Secure Your AWS Workloads</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_microsoft_defender_for_containers_to_secure_your_aws_workloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_microsoft_defender_for_containers_to_secure_your_aws_workloads/</guid>
      <description>Securing Containers in a Multicloud Environment with Microsoft Defender for Containers As organizations increasingly adopt container technologies and deploy workloads across multiple cloud providers, ensuring the security and visibility of these environments becomes a critical priority. Microsoft Defender for Containers, part of the Microsoft Defender for Cloud solution, provides a comprehensive, cloud-native approach to securing containers across Azure, AWS, and other cloud platforms.
Enabling Defender for Containers for Your AWS Accounts To get started with protecting your AWS-hosted containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to enable the Defender for Containers plan within your Microsoft Defender for Cloud environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>As cloud adoption continues to mature, organizations are finding themselves navigating an increasingly complex journey to the cloud. The hybrid and multicloud scenario presents both challenges and opportunities, requiring a strategic and well-orchestrated approach to succeed.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the key considerations and guidance necessary to prepare for and thrive in a hybrid and multicloud environment.
The Hybrid and Multicloud Scenario The hybrid and multicloud scenario is centered around two primary goals:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seamless Migration of Classic IaaS Resources to Azure Resource Manager</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/seamless_migration_of_classic_iaas_resources_to_azure_resource_manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/seamless_migration_of_classic_iaas_resources_to_azure_resource_manager/</guid>
      <description>Overview of Platform-Supported Migration As the cloud computing landscape evolves, Microsoft has introduced Azure Resource Manager (ARM) as the preferred deployment model, offering enhanced capabilities and benefits over the classic Azure Service Manager (ASM) model. Today, approximately 90% of IaaS VMs are using Azure Resource Manager, and the classic deployment model has been deprecated, with a full retirement scheduled for September 6, 2023.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the platform-supported migration process, enabling you to seamlessly transition your existing classic IaaS resources, including virtual machines, storage accounts, and virtual networks, to the Azure Resource Manager deployment model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your AWS Container Workloads with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_aws_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_aws_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Securing Your AWS Container Workloads with Microsoft Defender for Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your container-based applications, regardless of where they run. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to enable Defender for Containers for your Amazon Web Services (AWS) container workloads, ensuring your clusters, containers, and applications are protected.
Prerequisites Before getting started, make sure you have the following in place:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your Cloud Savings with Microsoft Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_savings_with_microsoft_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_savings_with_microsoft_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Power of Microsoft Cost Management Microsoft Cost Management is a comprehensive suite of FinOps tools designed to help organizations like yours analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud spending. With Cost Management, you can gain complete visibility into your cloud costs, proactively manage your budget, and unlock significant cost savings.
Understand the Commerce Data Pipeline At the heart of Cost Management is the Microsoft Commerce data pipeline, which powers all commercial transactions across Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data and Cross-Cloud Scaling</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_and_cross-cloud_scaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_and_cross-cloud_scaling/</guid>
      <description>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data and Cross-Cloud Scaling In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of deploying a hybrid application that leverages both Azure and Azure Stack Hub to create a scalable and resilient solution. By combining the benefits of a private cloud (Azure Stack Hub) with the scalability of the public cloud (Azure), you can build applications that meet your organization&amp;rsquo;s compliance requirements while still taking advantage of the cloud&amp;rsquo;s elasticity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging the Cluster Autoscaler to Optimize Kubernetes Costs on Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_the_cluster_autoscaler_to_optimize_kubernetes_costs_on_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/leveraging_the_cluster_autoscaler_to_optimize_kubernetes_costs_on_azure/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging the Cluster Autoscaler to Optimize Kubernetes Costs on Azure As organizations continue to embrace Kubernetes for their cloud-native applications, managing and optimizing the cost of running these environments becomes a critical concern. One of the key tools in the Kubernetes cost optimization arsenal is the Cluster Autoscaler (CA), a powerful component that can dynamically scale the number of nodes in your Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) cluster to match the changing demands of your workloads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Time-Series Forecasting with Azure Machine Learning&#39;s Automated ML</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_time-series_forecasting_with_azure_machine_learnings_automated_ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_time-series_forecasting_with_azure_machine_learnings_automated_ml/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into setting up Azure Machine Learning&amp;rsquo;s Automated ML for time-series forecasting. Unlike classical time series methods, Automated ML takes a unique approach by &amp;ldquo;pivoting&amp;rdquo; past time-series values to become additional dimensions for the regressor, along with other predictors. This approach allows Automated ML to incorporate multiple contextual variables and their relationships during training, making it a powerful tool for real-world forecasting scenarios.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start by preparing your data for time-series modeling, ensuring that all features used in training can be used when running predictions for your intended horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Virtual WAN- A Comprehensive Guide for Seamless Site-to-Site Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_virtual_wan_a_comprehensive_guide_for_seamless_site-to-site_connectivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_virtual_wan_a_comprehensive_guide_for_seamless_site-to-site_connectivity/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure Virtual WAN: A Comprehensive Guide for Seamless Site-to-Site Connectivity Azure Virtual WAN is a powerful and versatile networking service that simplifies the process of connecting your on-premises sites to Azure resources. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned networking professional or new to the cloud, this comprehensive guide will walk you through the step-by-step process of creating a secure, reliable, and scalable site-to-site connection using Virtual WAN.
Understanding Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a fully managed, software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) service that provides unified connectivity and security across your global network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing Your Environment for Hybrid and Multicloud Scenarios with Azure Arc</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_hybrid_and_multicloud_scenarios_with_azure_arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_your_environment_for_hybrid_and_multicloud_scenarios_with_azure_arc/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s ever-evolving technology landscape, organizations are increasingly adopting hybrid and multicloud strategies to meet their diverse business needs. The Cloud Adoption Framework&amp;rsquo;s Ready methodology provides a structured approach to prepare your environment for these complex scenarios, with Azure landing zones serving as the building blocks.
Understanding Hybrid and Multicloud in Azure Landing Zones Azure landing zones are the result of a multi-subscription Azure environment that accounts for scale, security governance, networking, identity, cost management, and monitoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Data Integration Power with Azure Integration Runtime</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_data_integration_power_with_azure_integration_runtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unlocking_data_integration_power_with_azure_integration_runtime/</guid>
      <description>Azure Integration Runtime: The Backbone of Azure Data Factory and Synapse Analytics
In the ever-evolving world of data integration, the Integration Runtime (IR) is the unsung hero, powering the data movement and transformation capabilities of Azure Data Factory and Azure Synapse Analytics. This guide will take you through the process of creating and configuring an Azure Integration Runtime, empowering you to unlock the full potential of your data integration projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Machine Learning Models with InterpretML</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unraveling_machine_learning_models_with_interpretml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/unraveling_machine_learning_models_with_interpretml/</guid>
      <description>Unraveling Machine Learning Models with InterpretML In the world of modern machine learning, models have become increasingly complex, often operating as opaque &amp;ldquo;black boxes&amp;rdquo; that deliver impressive results but leave us wondering about the inner workings that drive their decision-making. This poses a significant challenge, as understanding model behavior is crucial for building trust, debugging issues, and ensuring responsible AI deployment.
Enter InterpretML, an open-source toolkit that empowers data scientists, developers, and business stakeholders to gain comprehensive insights into their machine learning models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplify Your Azure Migration with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/simplify_your_azure_migration_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/simplify_your_azure_migration_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate: Your One-Stop Solution for Seamless Cloud Transformation
In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving digital landscape, organizations are constantly seeking efficient and reliable ways to migrate their on-premises infrastructure, data, and applications to the cloud. Azure Migrate, a comprehensive service from Microsoft, offers a streamlined approach to this critical journey.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate lies a single, centralized portal that empowers you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an internal load balancer in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_an_internal_load_balancer_in_azure_kubernetes_service_aks.2023-09-17t220900-0500/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 22:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/create_an_internal_load_balancer_in_azure_kubernetes_service_aks.2023-09-17t220900-0500/</guid>
      <description>As a cluster operator or developer, you may want to create a service in AKS that uses an internal Azure load balancer for enhanced security and without an external endpoint. This article shows you how to create and use an internal load balancer with AKS.
Before you begin  This article assumes that you have an existing AKS cluster. If you need an AKS cluster, you can create one using Azure CLI, Azure PowerShell, or the Azure portal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Containers- Best Practices for Container Image Management in Azure Kubernetes Service</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containers_best_practices_for_container_image_management_in_azure_kubernetes_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containers_best_practices_for_container_image_management_in_azure_kubernetes_service/</guid>
      <description>Containers and container image security are critical priorities when developing and running applications in Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS). Outdated base images or unpatched application runtimes introduce security risks and potential attack vectors. To minimize these risks, you can integrate and run scanning and remediation tools in your containers during both the build and runtime stages. The earlier you identify vulnerabilities or outdated base images, the more secure your application will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune for Enhanced Device Security</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/integrating_microsoft_defender_for_endpoint_with_microsoft_intune_for_enhanced_device_security/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/integrating_microsoft_defender_for_endpoint_with_microsoft_intune_for_enhanced_device_security/</guid>
      <description>Securing your organization&amp;rsquo;s devices against cyber threats is a critical priority in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Microsoft Intune, combined with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint, provides a powerful solution to enhance your device security posture. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the steps to configure the integration between these two Microsoft services, allowing you to effectively onboard devices, set compliance policies based on risk levels, and leverage conditional access to protect your corporate resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Releases of Eclipse Temurin - The Open Source Java SE Build</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/latest_releases_of_eclipse_temurin_-_the_open_source_java_se_build/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/latest_releases_of_eclipse_temurin_-_the_open_source_java_se_build/</guid>
      <description>The Adoptium website provides access to the latest releases of Eclipse Temurin, an open source Java SE build based on OpenJDK. Temurin is available for a wide range of platforms and Java SE versions, and the latest releases recommended for production use are listed on this page.
Some key details about the Temurin releases:
Latest Recommended Releases The page displays the current recommended Temurin releases for production use, which include versions 22, 21, 19, 18, 16, and 8 (LTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Container Workloads with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This article delves into the key capabilities of Defender for Containers and how it can help organizations address the evolving security challenges surrounding container-based solutions.
Core Elements of Defender for Containers Defender for Containers assists you with four core domains of container security:
1. Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides a range of agentless capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your container environments:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering NAT Rules for Your Azure Virtual WAN VPN Gateway</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_nat_rules_for_your_azure_virtual_wan_vpn_gateway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_nat_rules_for_your_azure_virtual_wan_vpn_gateway/</guid>
      <description>Mastering NAT Rules for Your Azure Virtual WAN VPN Gateway As organizations increasingly adopt cloud infrastructure, they often encounter the challenge of interconnecting their on-premises networks with Azure virtual networks. One common scenario is when branch offices have overlapping IP address spaces, making it difficult to establish direct connectivity. Fortunately, Azure Virtual WAN&amp;rsquo;s site-to-site VPN gateway offers a powerful solution - NAT (Network Address Translation) rules.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the ins and outs of configuring NAT rules for your Azure Virtual WAN VPN gateway, empowering you to seamlessly interconnect your on-premises networks with Azure resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Establish a Secure Site-to-Site VPN Connection for Azure VMware Solution</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/establish_a_secure_site-to-site_vpn_connection_for_azure_vmware_solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/establish_a_secure_site-to-site_vpn_connection_for_azure_vmware_solution/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of setting up a secure site-to-site VPN connection between your on-premises network and Azure VMware Solution. This powerful integration allows you to seamlessly extend your local infrastructure into the Azure cloud, enabling hybrid scenarios and providing a reliable, high-performance connection.
Prerequisites Before we begin, ensure that you have the following:
 A public-facing IP address for your on-premises VPN device. Familiarity with Azure Virtual WAN and its components, including virtual hubs and VPN gateways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating IaaS Resources from Classic to Azure Resource Manager- A Technical Deep Dive</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_iaas_resources_from_classic_to_azure_resource_manager_a_technical_deep_dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_iaas_resources_from_classic_to_azure_resource_manager_a_technical_deep_dive/</guid>
      <description>Migrating IaaS Resources from Classic to Azure Resource Manager: A Technical Deep Dive As the Azure platform continues to evolve, the migration from the classic deployment model to the Azure Resource Manager deployment model has become an important part of managing your cloud infrastructure. This comprehensive guide will take you on a deep dive into the technical aspects of this migration process, helping you understand how the Azure platform translates resources between the two deployment models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape with Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_with_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_with_azure/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape with Azure As enterprises increasingly look to leverage the benefits of cloud computing, many are finding that a hybrid or multicloud approach is the best fit for their needs. Microsoft Azure, as a leading enterprise-grade cloud provider, is well-equipped to support businesses across public, hybrid, and multicloud environments.
Understanding Hybrid and Multicloud A hybrid cloud combines a private cloud (on-premises infrastructure) with a public cloud (third-party cloud services).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the SUSE Customer Center- Your Gateway to SUSE Product Support and Resources</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_the_suse_customer_center_your_gateway_to_suse_product_support_and_resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_the_suse_customer_center_your_gateway_to_suse_product_support_and_resources/</guid>
      <description>As a SUSE customer, the SUSE Customer Center is your one-stop-shop for managing your SUSE product subscriptions, accessing technical support, and tapping into a wealth of resources to help you get the most out of your SUSE solutions. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the SUSE Customer Center, exploring its key features and capabilities to empower you as a SUSE user.
Navigating the SUSE Customer Center The SUSE Customer Center is accessible at https://scc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate- Simplifying Your Cloud Journey</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_journey/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful service that streamlines your migration, modernization, and optimization journey to the cloud. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to assess and migrate servers, databases, web apps, or virtual desktops, Azure Migrate provides a unified platform to get the job done efficiently.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate is a single portal that allows you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure. This centralized approach helps you stay on top of your cloud transformation efforts, regardless of the complexity or scale of your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Your Azure Costs with the Cost Optimization Workbook</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_azure_costs_with_the_cost_optimization_workbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_azure_costs_with_the_cost_optimization_workbook/</guid>
      <description>The Azure Cost Optimization workbook is a powerful tool designed to help you understand and optimize the costs of your Azure environment. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the features and capabilities of the workbook, empowering you to make informed decisions and drive cost savings in your Azure deployments.
Overview The Azure Cost Optimization workbook serves as a centralized hub for some of the most commonly used tools that can help you drive utilization and efficiency goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Azure Container Instances- Best Practices for Image Management and Container Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_best_practices_for_image_management_and_container_ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_best_practices_for_image_management_and_container_ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>Securing Azure Container Instances: Best Practices for Image Management and Container Ecosystem Containerizing your applications can bring tremendous benefits in terms of portability, scalability, and efficiency. However, it also introduces new security considerations that must be addressed to protect your Azure infrastructure and workloads. This comprehensive guide explores the key security recommendations for managing container images and the broader container ecosystem when using Azure Container Instances.
Secure Your Container Images Use a Private Container Registry Storing and retrieving container images from a private registry, such as Azure Container Registry or Docker Trusted Registry, is crucial for mitigating security risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Your Local Sites to Azure Using Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/connecting_your_local_sites_to_azure_using_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/connecting_your_local_sites_to_azure_using_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Azure Virtual WAN is a networking service that provides a simple, unified, and global connectivity solution for connecting your on-premises sites to Azure. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how you can leverage Virtual WAN to establish secure site-to-site VPN connections between your local network and your Azure resources.
Understanding Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a fully managed, software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) service that simplifies the process of connecting your branch offices, retail locations, and other remote sites to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Remote Access to Azure Resources Using Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_remote_access_to_azure_resources_using_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/secure_remote_access_to_azure_resources_using_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Secure Remote Access to Azure Resources Using Azure Virtual WAN In today&amp;rsquo;s increasingly distributed work environment, providing secure remote access to corporate resources has become a critical priority for organizations. Azure Virtual WAN offers a powerful solution to this challenge, enabling you to create point-to-site (P2S) User VPN connections that allow remote users to securely access your Azure resources.
Overview of Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a networking service that simplifies the creation and management of wide-area networks (WANs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Amazon Web Service (AWS) Containers with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_amazon_web_service_aws_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_amazon_web_service_aws_containers_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Securing Your Amazon Web Service (AWS) Containers with Microsoft Defender for Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers is a cloud-native solution that helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your Kubernetes clusters, containers, and their applications across multi-cloud and hybrid environments.
Prerequisites Before you can enable Defender for Containers on your AWS account, make sure you have:
 A Microsoft Azure subscription. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you can sign up for a free Azure subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize and Manage Costs for Azure App Service</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_and_manage_costs_for_azure_app_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_and_manage_costs_for_azure_app_service/</guid>
      <description>Azure App Service is a powerful and flexible platform for hosting web applications, APIs, and mobile backends in the cloud. However, as with any cloud service, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand and manage the costs associated with using App Service. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to plan, optimize, and monitor costs for your Azure App Service deployments.
Understanding the App Service Billing Model When you use Azure App Service, you&amp;rsquo;re charged based on several factors:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize Your Microsoft Sentinel Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_microsoft_sentinel_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_microsoft_sentinel_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the costs associated with Microsoft Sentinel can be a complex task, but with the right strategies, you can significantly reduce your expenses. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore various methods to optimize your Microsoft Sentinel costs and ensure you get the most value from your investment.
Set or Change Pricing Tier To achieve the highest savings, closely monitor your data ingestion volume and ensure you have the Commitment Tier that aligns most closely with your usage patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data that Scales Across Clouds</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive guide shows you how to deploy a hybrid app that spans both Azure and Azure Stack Hub and uses a single on-premises data source. By using a hybrid cloud solution, you can combine the compliance benefits of a private cloud with the scalability of the public cloud. Your developers can also take advantage of the Microsoft developer ecosystem and apply their skills to the cloud and on-premises environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize your cloud investment with Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_cloud_investment_with_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_your_cloud_investment_with_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Optimize your cloud investment with Cost Management Cost Management gives you the tools to plan for, analyze and reduce your spending to maximize your cloud investment. This document provides you with a methodical approach to cost management and highlights the tools available to you as you address your organization&amp;rsquo;s cost challenges. Azure makes it easy to build and deploy cloud solutions. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important that those solutions are optimized to minimize the cost to your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Cloud Deployment Models- Public, Private, and Hybrid Strategies</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid_strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_cloud_deployment_models_public_private_and_hybrid_strategies/</guid>
      <description>As organizations navigate the digital landscape, the choice of cloud deployment model has become a critical decision. The options span public, private, and hybrid clouds, each offering unique advantages and considerations. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the nuances of these cloud deployment models, equipping you with the knowledge to make an informed decision that aligns with your business needs.
Public Cloud: Scalability and Convenience The public cloud has emerged as the most prevalent deployment model, providing organizations with a highly scalable and agile infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Forecasting with Lags and Rolling Window Features</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/advanced_forecasting_with_lags_and_rolling_window_features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/advanced_forecasting_with_lags_and_rolling_window_features/</guid>
      <description>In this notebook, we&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to use Azure Machine Learning&amp;rsquo;s automated machine learning (AutoML) for time-series forecasting, with a focus on manually configuring lag and rolling window features.
Prepare Data We&amp;rsquo;ll start by loading the energy demand data into an MLTable, which is the required format for AutoML forecasting jobs.
import pandas as pd from azure.ai.ml import Input from azure.ai.ml.constants import AssetTypes # Load the energy demand data df = pd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender for Cloud Pricing- Comprehensive Security at Scale</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/microsoft_defender_for_cloud_pricing_comprehensive_security_at_scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/microsoft_defender_for_cloud_pricing_comprehensive_security_at_scale/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Cloud is a unified, cloud-native security platform that provides advanced protection for your multicloud and hybrid environments. With flexible pricing options, you can tailor your security coverage to your specific needs and budget.
Cloud Security Posture Management (CSPM) Microsoft Defender for Cloud offers both foundational and advanced CSPM capabilities:
 Foundational CSPM: This is available for free and includes continuous security assessments, security recommendations, Secure Score, and the Microsoft cloud security benchmark across Azure, AWS, and Google Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Maximizing Azure Cost Management Reporting</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_and_maximizing_azure_cost_management_reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_and_maximizing_azure_cost_management_reporting/</guid>
      <description>Azure Cost Management is a powerful suite of tools that helps you gain visibility into your cloud spending, identify cost savings opportunities, and optimize your cloud infrastructure. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key reporting components of Azure Cost Management and how to leverage them to make informed decisions about your cloud investments.
Cost Analysis: Visualize and Analyze Your Costs Cost analysis should be your first stop when it comes to understanding your cloud spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demand Forecasting with Holiday Detection and Featurization</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/demand_forecasting_with_holiday_detection_and_featurization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/demand_forecasting_with_holiday_detection_and_featurization/</guid>
      <description>In this notebook, we&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate how to use Azure Machine Learning&amp;rsquo;s automated machine learning (AutoML) for time-series forecasting, with a focus on handling holidays and creating custom features.
Prepare Data We&amp;rsquo;ll start by loading the bike share demand data into an MLTable, which is the required format for AutoML forecasting jobs. We&amp;rsquo;ll also add a &amp;lsquo;holiday&amp;rsquo; column to the data, which will be used later for feature engineering.
import pandas as pd from azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessing and Migrating Applications to Azure - A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/assessing_and_migrating_applications_to_azure_-_a_step-by-step_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/assessing_and_migrating_applications_to_azure_-_a_step-by-step_guide/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the process of assessing an on-premises multi-tier application and migrating it to Microsoft Azure. We&amp;rsquo;ll leverage the powerful suite of tools provided by Azure Migrate to ensure a seamless and efficient migration journey.
Abstract and Learning Objectives This hands-on lab will teach you how to assess and migrate a multi-tier application from Hyper-V to Azure. You will learn to use Azure Migrate as the central hub for executing the migration, along with accompanying tools like Microsoft Data Migration Assistant (DMA) and Azure Database Migration Service (DMS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage and Monitor Costs for Microsoft Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_and_monitor_costs_for_microsoft_sentinel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/manage_and_monitor_costs_for_microsoft_sentinel/</guid>
      <description>Manage and Monitor Costs for Microsoft Sentinel As you use Microsoft Sentinel, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand and manage the associated costs. Microsoft Sentinel costs are only a portion of your overall Azure bill, but it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to monitor them closely to avoid unexpected expenses. This comprehensive guide will walk you through various strategies and tools to help you manage and monitor Microsoft Sentinel costs effectively.
View Costs Using Cost Analysis The Azure portal&amp;rsquo;s Cost Management features allow you to view, analyze, and monitor your Microsoft Sentinel costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Azure Hybrid Benefit Management for Significant Cost Savings</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_azure_hybrid_benefit_management_for_significant_cost_savings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_azure_hybrid_benefit_management_for_significant_cost_savings/</guid>
      <description>Centralizing Azure Hybrid Benefit Management for SQL Server Azure Hybrid Benefit is a powerful licensing program that allows you to significantly reduce the costs of running your workloads in the cloud. By bringing your on-premises Software Assurance or subscription-enabled Windows Server and SQL Server licenses to Azure, you can save substantially on your cloud computing expenses.
One of the key advancements in Azure Hybrid Benefit is the introduction of centralized management capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
