<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modernization on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/modernization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modernization on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/modernization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Discover, Assess, and Migrate to Azure with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/discover_assess_and_migrate_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/discover_assess_and_migrate_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that simplifies the process of migrating, modernizing, and optimizing your infrastructure, data, and applications for Azure. This comprehensive service provides a unified portal to streamline your entire cloud migration journey.
Unified Migration Platform Azure Migrate offers a centralized hub where you can start, run, and track your migration to Azure. It provides a range of assessment and migration tools, including Azure Migrate: Discovery and Assessment, and Migration and Modernization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Your Linux Workloads to Azure</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/migrating_your_linux_workloads_to_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/migrating_your_linux_workloads_to_azure/</guid>
      <description>Azure offers a proven and reliable platform for running your Linux workloads. With a rich ecosystem of supported Linux distributions, flexible licensing options, and robust security features, Azure is an excellent choice for migrating and modernizing your mission-critical Linux applications.
Migrate to Innovate Azure provides a seamless path for migrating your on-premises Linux workloads to the cloud. Using tools like Azure Migrate, you can assess your existing environment, plan your migration, and then execute the migration process with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate- Simplifying Your Cloud Migration Journey</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_migration_journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_migration_journey/</guid>
      <description>A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate: Simplifying Your Cloud Migration Journey Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that provides a simplified and streamlined approach to migrating, modernizing, and optimizing your infrastructure, data, and applications for the Azure cloud. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to migrate on-premises servers, databases, web apps, or virtual desktops, Azure Migrate offers a comprehensive suite of tools and services to make your cloud journey a success.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate is a single, unified portal that allows you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplify Your Azure Migration with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/simplify_your_azure_migration_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/simplify_your_azure_migration_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate: Your One-Stop Solution for Seamless Cloud Transformation
In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving digital landscape, organizations are constantly seeking efficient and reliable ways to migrate their on-premises infrastructure, data, and applications to the cloud. Azure Migrate, a comprehensive service from Microsoft, offers a streamlined approach to this critical journey.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate lies a single, centralized portal that empowers you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Azure Migrate- Simplifying Your Cloud Journey</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/a_comprehensive_guide_to_azure_migrate_simplifying_your_cloud_journey/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful service that streamlines your migration, modernization, and optimization journey to the cloud. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to assess and migrate servers, databases, web apps, or virtual desktops, Azure Migrate provides a unified platform to get the job done efficiently.
Unified Migration Platform At the heart of Azure Migrate is a single portal that allows you to start, run, and track your migration to Azure. This centralized approach helps you stay on top of your cloud transformation efforts, regardless of the complexity or scale of your on-premises infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
