<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cloud operations on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/cloud-operations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cloud operations on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/cloud-operations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Journey- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_journey_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>As organizations continue to embrace cloud computing, the path to cloud adoption is becoming increasingly complex. The hybrid and multicloud scenario, as outlined in the Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure, presents a strategic approach to navigating this evolving landscape.
This comprehensive guide aims to provide a deep dive into the key components and considerations required to successfully implement a hybrid and multicloud strategy.
Understanding the Hybrid and Multicloud Scenario The hybrid and multicloud scenario focuses on two primary objectives:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Hybrid and Multicloud Landscape- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/navigating_the_hybrid_and_multicloud_landscape_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>As cloud adoption continues to mature, organizations are finding themselves navigating an increasingly complex journey to the cloud. The hybrid and multicloud scenario presents both challenges and opportunities, requiring a strategic and well-orchestrated approach to succeed.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the key considerations and guidance necessary to prepare for and thrive in a hybrid and multicloud environment.
The Hybrid and Multicloud Scenario The hybrid and multicloud scenario is centered around two primary goals:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
