<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubuntu on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/ubuntu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ubuntu on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/ubuntu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installing PowerShell on Linux- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_on_linux_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>PowerShell is a powerful and versatile tool that can be installed on a variety of Linux distributions, each with its own package manager and installation process. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the supported Linux distributions and the steps to install PowerShell on each of them.
Supported Linux Distributions PowerShell can be installed on several different Linux distributions, including:
Alpine Alpine is a lightweight and secure Linux distribution that uses the APK package manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing PowerShell Core on Ubuntu Linux</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_core_on_ubuntu_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/installing_powershell_core_on_ubuntu_linux/</guid>
      <description>Installing PowerShell Core on Ubuntu Linux If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to get started with PowerShell on Linux, specifically Ubuntu, this guide has you covered. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through installing the necessary dependencies, setting up PowerShell Core, and configuring Visual Studio Code (VSCode) for editing PowerShell scripts.
Install Useful Tools Before we install PowerShell Core, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure we have some helpful tools in place. We&amp;rsquo;ll start by updating the package manager:
sudo apt-get -y update Next, let&amp;rsquo;s install a few key tools:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
