<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Budget Alerts on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/budget-alerts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Budget Alerts on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/budget-alerts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Cost Management Alerts- Monitoring Usage and Spending with Precision</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_cost_management_alerts_monitoring_usage_and_spending_with_precision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_cost_management_alerts_monitoring_usage_and_spending_with_precision/</guid>
      <description>Effective cost management is crucial for organizations leveraging the power of Microsoft Azure. One of the key tools in the Cost Management arsenal is the ability to set up cost alerts, which can help you stay on top of your Azure usage and spending. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the different types of cost alerts, their capabilities, and how to leverage them to gain better control over your Azure costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cost Automation- Unlock the Power of Programmatic Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Maximizing the value of your cloud investment requires a strategic approach to cost management. Azure offers a robust set of automation tools and APIs that enable you to streamline your cost data retrieval, analysis, and alerting processes. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various techniques and best practices for automating your Azure cost management workflows.
Automate Cost Data Retrieval for Offline Analysis Integrating your Azure cost data with other datasets or internal systems can provide valuable insights to drive key business decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
