<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alerts on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/alerts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in alerts on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/alerts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create and Manage Budgets in Azure Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/create_and_manage_budgets_in_azure_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/create_and_manage_budgets_in_azure_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Creating and Managing Budgets in Azure Cost Management Budgets in Azure Cost Management help you plan for and manage your organizational spending on Azure services. They enable you to proactively monitor costs, set spending limits, and receive alerts when thresholds are exceeded. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of creating, configuring, and managing budgets in the Azure portal.
Prerequisites  Understand the different Azure account types and scopes that support budgets, including Azure RBAC, Enterprise Agreement, Individual, and Microsoft Customer Agreement scopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN When you have critical applications and business processes relying on Azure resources, it&amp;rsquo;s important to monitor those resources for their availability and performance. This article will guide you through the monitoring data generated by Azure Virtual WAN and how to leverage Azure Monitor to gain visibility into your Virtual WAN deployment.
Prerequisites To follow along, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have an existing Virtual WAN deployment configured. If you need help with that, check out these guides:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Monitor Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/optimizing_azure_monitor_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/optimizing_azure_monitor_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Cost-Effective Monitoring with Azure Monitor Azure Monitor is a powerful tool that provides comprehensive observability into your applications, infrastructure, and network. However, with its varied pricing models and features, understanding and optimizing your Azure Monitor costs can be a challenge. In this in-depth guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the different components of Azure Monitor pricing, share strategies to analyze and manage your costs, and provide practical tips to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the most out of your Azure Monitor investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage and Optimize Azure Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/manage_and_optimize_azure_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/manage_and_optimize_azure_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Manage and Optimize Azure Costs: A Comprehensive Guide When you sign up for Azure, it&amp;rsquo;s important to get a handle on your spending and proactively manage costs. This comprehensive guide will walk you through key strategies and tools to plan, monitor, and optimize your Azure expenditure.
Get Estimated Costs Before Adding Azure Services Before provisioning any Azure resources, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to estimate the potential costs. You can use the following tools to get accurate estimates:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cost Management- Creating and Managing Budgets</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_azure_cost_management_creating_and_managing_budgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_azure_cost_management_creating_and_managing_budgets/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure Cost Management: Creating and Managing Budgets Budgets in Azure Cost Management are a powerful tool to help you plan, monitor, and control your cloud spending. By creating and managing budgets, you can proactively inform your organization about spending, manage costs, and track how spending evolves over time.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of creating and managing budgets in the Azure portal, as well as exploring programmatic options using PowerShell, CLI, and Terraform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage and Monitor Costs for Microsoft Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/manage_and_monitor_costs_for_microsoft_sentinel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/manage_and_monitor_costs_for_microsoft_sentinel/</guid>
      <description>Manage and Monitor Costs for Microsoft Sentinel As you use Microsoft Sentinel, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand and manage the associated costs. Microsoft Sentinel costs are only a portion of your overall Azure bill, but it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to monitor them closely to avoid unexpected expenses. This comprehensive guide will walk you through various strategies and tools to help you manage and monitor Microsoft Sentinel costs effectively.
View Costs Using Cost Analysis The Azure portal&amp;rsquo;s Cost Management features allow you to view, analyze, and monitor your Microsoft Sentinel costs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
