<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Cost Management on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/azure-cost-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Cost Management on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/azure-cost-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Azure Cost Management for Partners</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_azure_cost_management_for_partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_azure_cost_management_for_partners/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with Azure Cost Management for Partners As a Microsoft partner, Azure Cost Management is a powerful tool that can help you effectively manage and monitor your customers&#39; cloud costs. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the key features and capabilities of Cost Management, and how you can leverage them to gain visibility, control, and optimization of your customers&#39; Azure spending.
Understanding Cost Management Scopes In Cost Management, there are two main types of scopes: billing scopes and Azure RBAC scopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Costs with Recommendation-Driven Actions</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendation-driven_actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendation-driven_actions/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Azure Costs with Recommendation-Driven Actions Managing cloud costs effectively is a critical concern for organizations leveraging Azure services. This comprehensive guide takes you through the process of identifying and acting on cost optimization recommendations provided by Azure Advisor, helping you reduce your Azure spending.
Unlock Savings with Azure Advisor Recommendations Azure Advisor is a powerful tool that works in tandem with Azure Cost Management to provide tailored cost optimization recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Microsoft Cost Management- Optimize Your Cloud Spending</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_cost_management_optimize_your_cloud_spending/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_microsoft_cost_management_optimize_your_cloud_spending/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Cost Management is a powerful suite of FinOps tools that empowers organizations to analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud costs. This comprehensive platform provides a centralized view of your cloud spending, enabling you to make data-driven decisions and achieve cost optimization at scale.
Understanding the Commerce Data Pipeline At the core of Cost Management is the Microsoft Commerce data pipeline, which processes and tracks all commercial transactions, from consumer to enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Cost Management Alerts- Monitoring Usage and Spending with Precision</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_cost_management_alerts_monitoring_usage_and_spending_with_precision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_cost_management_alerts_monitoring_usage_and_spending_with_precision/</guid>
      <description>Effective cost management is crucial for organizations leveraging the power of Microsoft Azure. One of the key tools in the Cost Management arsenal is the ability to set up cost alerts, which can help you stay on top of your Azure usage and spending. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the different types of cost alerts, their capabilities, and how to leverage them to gain better control over your Azure costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your Cloud Efficiency with Microsoft Azure Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_efficiency_with_microsoft_azure_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_efficiency_with_microsoft_azure_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the world of cloud computing can be a daunting task, especially when it comes to understanding and managing your cloud costs. That&amp;rsquo;s where Microsoft Azure Cost Management comes in - a powerful suite of FinOps tools designed to help organizations like yours analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud spending.
In this comprehensive post, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the ins and outs of Azure Cost Management, exploring how it can help you take control of your cloud costs and drive greater efficiency across your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Costs with Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimizing_azure_costs_with_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Effectively managing and optimizing cloud costs is a crucial aspect of any successful Azure deployment. This comprehensive tutorial will guide you through the process of identifying and acting on cost optimization recommendations provided by Azure Advisor, helping you reduce your Azure expenditure.
Unlocking Cost Savings with Azure Advisor Azure Advisor, a powerful tool integrated with Cost Management, analyzes your resource utilization and identifies areas where you can optimize your spending. By reviewing the cost optimization recommendations, you can uncover opportunities to resize underutilized virtual machines, purchase Azure Savings Plans, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Your FinOps Practice with Improved Azure Cost Management Exports</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</guid>
      <description>Azure&amp;rsquo;s Cost Management service has recently introduced an &amp;ldquo;Improved Exports&amp;rdquo; experience that aims to simplify and enhance the process of exporting cost and usage data for FinOps professionals. This new feature offers a range of improvements designed to help organizations better manage their cloud spending and optimize their cloud investments.
The Improved Exports experience provides several key benefits:
Expanded Dataset Support The enhanced exports feature now supports a wider range of datasets, including price sheets, reservation recommendations, reservation details, and reservation transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Azure Costs with Optimization Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/reduce_azure_costs_with_optimization_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/reduce_azure_costs_with_optimization_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing your Azure costs can have a significant impact on your overall cloud spending. This comprehensive guide walks you through leveraging Azure Advisor recommendations to identify and address underutilized resources, ultimately helping you reduce your Azure costs.
Understand Cost Optimization Recommendations Azure Advisor, integrated with Cost Management, provides valuable recommendations to help you optimize your Azure resource utilization and costs. These recommendations identify usage inefficiencies and potential savings opportunities.
The recommendations are categorized by their potential impact:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cost Automation- Unlock the Power of Programmatic Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Maximizing the value of your cloud investment requires a strategic approach to cost management. Azure offers a robust set of automation tools and APIs that enable you to streamline your cost data retrieval, analysis, and alerting processes. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various techniques and best practices for automating your Azure cost management workflows.
Automate Cost Data Retrieval for Offline Analysis Integrating your Azure cost data with other datasets or internal systems can provide valuable insights to drive key business decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your Cloud Savings with Microsoft Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_savings_with_microsoft_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_your_cloud_savings_with_microsoft_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the Power of Microsoft Cost Management Microsoft Cost Management is a comprehensive suite of FinOps tools designed to help organizations like yours analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud spending. With Cost Management, you can gain complete visibility into your cloud costs, proactively manage your budget, and unlock significant cost savings.
Understand the Commerce Data Pipeline At the heart of Cost Management is the Microsoft Commerce data pipeline, which powers all commercial transactions across Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
