<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes Security on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/kubernetes-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes Security on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/kubernetes-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Securing Containerized Applications with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_containerized_applications_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_containerized_applications_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This powerful platform provides a range of security capabilities to help you protect your Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images.
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers offers both agentless and sensor-based capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your containerized environment:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Containerized Assets with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containerized_assets_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_containerized_assets_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses four core domains of container security:
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers offers both agentless and sensor-based capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your containerized environment:
Agentless Capabilities:
 Agentless Discovery for Kubernetes: Provides zero-footprint, API-based discovery of your Kubernetes clusters, their configurations, and deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Your Containerized Infrastructure with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive, cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets, including Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images, across multicloud and on-premises environments.
Four Core Domains of Container Security Defender for Containers assists you with four key areas of container security:
  Security Posture Management:
 Provides continuous monitoring of cloud and Kubernetes APIs to discover resources, offer comprehensive inventory capabilities, detect misconfigurations, and provide guidelines to mitigate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Container Security with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_container_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_container_security_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses four core domains of container security: security posture management, vulnerability assessment, runtime threat protection, and deployment and monitoring.
Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides agentless capabilities that enable zero-footprint, API-based discovery of your Kubernetes clusters, their configurations, and deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Guide to Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/comprehensive_guide_to_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Microsoft Defender for Containers Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform addresses the unique security challenges associated with the rapid growth and adoption of containers and Kubernetes.
Defender for Containers provides a holistic approach to container security, focusing on four core domains:
  Security Posture Management: Continuously monitors cloud APIs, Kubernetes APIs, and Kubernetes workloads to discover resources, detect misconfigurations, provide risk assessment, and enable enhanced risk hunting capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Container Workloads with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This article delves into the key capabilities of Defender for Containers and how it can help organizations address the evolving security challenges surrounding container-based solutions.
Core Elements of Defender for Containers Defender for Containers assists you with four core domains of container security:
1. Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides a range of agentless capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your container environments:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
