<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>metrics on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/metrics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in metrics on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/metrics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN When you have critical applications and business processes relying on Azure resources, it&amp;rsquo;s important to monitor those resources for their availability and performance. This article will guide you through the monitoring data generated by Azure Virtual WAN and how to leverage Azure Monitor to gain visibility into your Virtual WAN deployment.
Prerequisites To follow along, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have an existing Virtual WAN deployment configured. If you need help with that, check out these guides:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Azure Monitor Costs- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/optimizing_azure_monitor_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/optimizing_azure_monitor_costs_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Cost-Effective Monitoring with Azure Monitor Azure Monitor is a powerful tool that provides comprehensive observability into your applications, infrastructure, and network. However, with its varied pricing models and features, understanding and optimizing your Azure Monitor costs can be a challenge. In this in-depth guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the different components of Azure Monitor pricing, share strategies to analyze and manage your costs, and provide practical tips to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the most out of your Azure Monitor investment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
