<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Migration on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/data-migration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Migration on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/data-migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Azure DevOps Services- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_to_azure_devops_services_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/migrating_to_azure_devops_services_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Migrating to Azure DevOps Services: A Comprehensive Guide Moving your on-premises Azure DevOps Server to the cloud-based Azure DevOps Services is a strategic decision that can unlock a world of benefits for your organization. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the entire migration process, from understanding the basics to completing the post-migration tasks.
Understanding the Migration Process Before embarking on your migration journey, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to familiarize yourself with the key concepts and considerations involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for a Seamless Migration to Azure DevOps Services</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_for_a_seamless_migration_to_azure_devops_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/preparing_for_a_seamless_migration_to_azure_devops_services/</guid>
      <description>Before you embark on your migration journey from Azure DevOps Server to the cloud-hosted Azure DevOps Services, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to understand the key concepts and considerations to ensure a successful transition. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the essential steps to get started with the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool and navigate the intricacies of the migration process.
Understanding the Data Migration Process The migration from Azure DevOps Server to Azure DevOps Services is not a one-size-fits-all process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Migrating to Azure DevOps Services</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_migrating_to_azure_devops_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_migrating_to_azure_devops_services/</guid>
      <description>Before you use the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool to migrate your database with high fidelity, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand some key concepts and considerations.
Included and Excluded Data Not all data gets migrated when moving from Azure DevOps Server to Azure DevOps Services. The migration process includes your team project collection, which contains work items, version control history, build definitions, and more. However, certain data is excluded, such as extensions, service hooks, load test data, pipeline agents/pools, and project server integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover, Assess, and Migrate to Azure with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/discover_assess_and_migrate_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/discover_assess_and_migrate_to_azure_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that simplifies the process of migrating, modernizing, and optimizing your infrastructure, data, and applications for Azure. This comprehensive service provides a unified portal to streamline your entire cloud migration journey.
Unified Migration Platform Azure Migrate offers a centralized hub where you can start, run, and track your migration to Azure. It provides a range of assessment and migration tools, including Azure Migrate: Discovery and Assessment, and Migration and Modernization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure DevOps Data Migration- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_devops_data_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_devops_data_migration_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure DevOps Data Migration: A Comprehensive Guide Before embarking on your Azure DevOps data migration journey, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the key concepts and considerations that will ensure a successful transition from your on-premises server to the cloud-based Azure DevOps Services.
Understanding the Migration Process The Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool facilitates a high-fidelity migration, ensuring that the majority of your data is seamlessly transferred to the cloud. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to note that not all data is migrated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoothly Migrate Your On-Premises Azure DevOps Server to the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/smoothly_migrate_your_on-premises_azure_devops_server_to_the_cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/smoothly_migrate_your_on-premises_azure_devops_server_to_the_cloud/</guid>
      <description>Before you use the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool to migrate your database with high fidelity, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the key concepts and considerations involved in the migration process.
Understand What Data Gets Migrated Not all data gets migrated during the process. Separate databases outside the collection, such as reporting and SharePoint data, do not get migrated. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what is and isn&amp;rsquo;t included:
Included Data
 Collection Mapping: Each collection in Azure DevOps Server corresponds to one database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Azure DevOps Data Migration</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_azure_devops_data_migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/get_started_with_azure_devops_data_migration/</guid>
      <description>Get Started with Azure DevOps Data Migration Before you use the Azure DevOps Data Migration Tool to migrate your database with high fidelity, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand some key concepts.
What Data Gets Migrated? Not all data gets migrated during the process. Separate databases outside the collection, such as reporting and SharePoint data, don&amp;rsquo;t get migrated. Here&amp;rsquo;s more detail on what does and doesn&amp;rsquo;t get migrated:
Included Data  Collection Mapping: Each collection in Azure DevOps Server corresponds to one database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplify Your Cloud Migration Journey with Azure Migrate</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/simplify_your_cloud_migration_journey_with_azure_migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/simplify_your_cloud_migration_journey_with_azure_migrate/</guid>
      <description>Streamlining the Migration to Azure Azure Migrate provides a comprehensive solution to simplify your journey to the cloud. This powerful service offers a range of tools and capabilities to help you assess, migrate, and modernize your on-premises infrastructure, data, and applications.
Unified Migration Platform Azure Migrate acts as a single portal to start, run, and track your migration to Azure. It provides a seamless experience, allowing you to manage the entire migration process from a centralized location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamline Your Data Migration to Azure Storage with AzCopy</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamline_your_data_migration_to_azure_storage_with_azcopy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamline_your_data_migration_to_azure_storage_with_azcopy/</guid>
      <description>Streamline Your Data Migration to Azure Storage with AzCopy Are you looking to move your on-premises data to the cloud? Azure Storage&amp;rsquo;s AzCopy tool can make the process quick and efficient. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to seamlessly migrate your data to Azure Storage using AzCopy.
What is AzCopy? AzCopy is a powerful command-line tool that allows you to copy data to and from Azure Blob storage, Azure Files, and Azure Table storage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
