<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Exports on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/data-exports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Exports on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/data-exports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Your FinOps Practice with Improved Azure Cost Management Exports</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/streamlining_your_finops_practice_with_improved_azure_cost_management_exports/</guid>
      <description>Azure&amp;rsquo;s Cost Management service has recently introduced an &amp;ldquo;Improved Exports&amp;rdquo; experience that aims to simplify and enhance the process of exporting cost and usage data for FinOps professionals. This new feature offers a range of improvements designed to help organizations better manage their cloud spending and optimize their cloud investments.
The Improved Exports experience provides several key benefits:
Expanded Dataset Support The enhanced exports feature now supports a wider range of datasets, including price sheets, reservation recommendations, reservation details, and reservation transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Cost Automation- Unlock the Power of Programmatic Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_cost_automation_unlock_the_power_of_programmatic_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Maximizing the value of your cloud investment requires a strategic approach to cost management. Azure offers a robust set of automation tools and APIs that enable you to streamline your cost data retrieval, analysis, and alerting processes. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the various techniques and best practices for automating your Azure cost management workflows.
Automate Cost Data Retrieval for Offline Analysis Integrating your Azure cost data with other datasets or internal systems can provide valuable insights to drive key business decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
