<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>threat protection on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/threat-protection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in threat protection on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/threat-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Your Containerized Infrastructure with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/safeguarding_your_containerized_infrastructure_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive, cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets, including Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images, across multicloud and on-premises environments.
Four Core Domains of Container Security Defender for Containers assists you with four key areas of container security:
  Security Posture Management:
 Provides continuous monitoring of cloud and Kubernetes APIs to discover resources, offer comprehensive inventory capabilities, detect misconfigurations, and provide guidelines to mitigate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Microsoft Defender for Endpoint with Microsoft Intune for Enhanced Device Security</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/integrating_microsoft_defender_for_endpoint_with_microsoft_intune_for_enhanced_device_security/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/integrating_microsoft_defender_for_endpoint_with_microsoft_intune_for_enhanced_device_security/</guid>
      <description>Securing your organization&amp;rsquo;s devices against cyber threats is a critical priority in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Microsoft Intune, combined with Microsoft Defender for Endpoint, provides a powerful solution to enhance your device security posture. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the steps to configure the integration between these two Microsoft services, allowing you to effectively onboard devices, set compliance policies based on risk levels, and leverage conditional access to protect your corporate resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Container Workloads with Microsoft Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_your_container_workloads_with_microsoft_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution designed to improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This article delves into the key capabilities of Defender for Containers and how it can help organizations address the evolving security challenges surrounding container-based solutions.
Core Elements of Defender for Containers Defender for Containers assists you with four core domains of container security:
1. Security Posture Management Defender for Containers provides a range of agentless capabilities to help you manage the security posture of your container environments:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
