<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Monitoring on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/monitoring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Monitoring on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptive Practices for Deploying and Running Azure Databricks at Scale</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/prescriptive_practices_for_deploying_and_running_azure_databricks_at_scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/prescriptive_practices_for_deploying_and_running_azure_databricks_at_scale/</guid>
      <description>Planning, deploying, and running Azure Databricks (ADB) at scale requires one to make many architectural decisions. While each ADB deployment is unique to an organization&amp;rsquo;s needs, we have found that some patterns are common across most successful ADB projects. This guide summarizes these patterns into prescriptive and actionable best practices for Azure Databricks.
We follow a logical path of planning the infrastructure, provisioning the workspaces, developing Azure Databricks applications, and finally, running Azure Databricks in production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/monitoring_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Monitoring Azure Virtual WAN When you have critical applications and business processes relying on Azure resources, it&amp;rsquo;s important to monitor those resources for their availability and performance. This article will guide you through the monitoring data generated by Azure Virtual WAN and how to leverage Azure Monitor to gain visibility into your Virtual WAN deployment.
Prerequisites To follow along, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have an existing Virtual WAN deployment configured. If you need help with that, check out these guides:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Azure Container Instances- Best Practices and Strategies</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/securing_your_azure_container_instances_best_practices_and_strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/securing_your_azure_container_instances_best_practices_and_strategies/</guid>
      <description>Containerization has revolutionized the way we develop, deploy, and manage applications, but with this powerful technology comes a unique set of security challenges. As organizations embrace Azure Container Instances to run their containerized workloads, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to address these security concerns head-on.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the security considerations for Azure Container Instances, equipping you with the knowledge and strategies to safeguard your containerized environments.
Securing Container Images Use a Private Registry Publicly available container images may not always be secure, as they can contain vulnerabilities in their various software layers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Azure Container Instances- Best Practices for Image Management and Container Ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_best_practices_for_image_management_and_container_ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_best_practices_for_image_management_and_container_ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>Securing Azure Container Instances: Best Practices for Image Management and Container Ecosystem Containerizing your applications can bring tremendous benefits in terms of portability, scalability, and efficiency. However, it also introduces new security considerations that must be addressed to protect your Azure infrastructure and workloads. This comprehensive guide explores the key security recommendations for managing container images and the broader container ecosystem when using Azure Container Instances.
Secure Your Container Images Use a Private Container Registry Storing and retrieving container images from a private registry, such as Azure Container Registry or Docker Trusted Registry, is crucial for mitigating security risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data that Scales Across Clouds</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive guide shows you how to deploy a hybrid app that spans both Azure and Azure Stack Hub and uses a single on-premises data source. By using a hybrid cloud solution, you can combine the compliance benefits of a private cloud with the scalability of the public cloud. Your developers can also take advantage of the Microsoft developer ecosystem and apply their skills to the cloud and on-premises environments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
