<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Stack Hub on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/azure-stack-hub/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Stack Hub on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/azure-stack-hub/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data and Cross-Cloud Scaling</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_and_cross-cloud_scaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_and_cross-cloud_scaling/</guid>
      <description>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data and Cross-Cloud Scaling In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of deploying a hybrid application that leverages both Azure and Azure Stack Hub to create a scalable and resilient solution. By combining the benefits of a private cloud (Azure Stack Hub) with the scalability of the public cloud (Azure), you can build applications that meet your organization&amp;rsquo;s compliance requirements while still taking advantage of the cloud&amp;rsquo;s elasticity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data that Scales Across Clouds</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive guide shows you how to deploy a hybrid app that spans both Azure and Azure Stack Hub and uses a single on-premises data source. By using a hybrid cloud solution, you can combine the compliance benefits of a private cloud with the scalability of the public cloud. Your developers can also take advantage of the Microsoft developer ecosystem and apply their skills to the cloud and on-premises environments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
