<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scalability on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/scalability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scalability on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/scalability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Serverless Computing on Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_on_microsoft_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_on_microsoft_azure/</guid>
      <description>Serverless computing is a revolutionary approach to application development that enables developers to build and run applications without having to manage any underlying infrastructure. This article provides an in-depth look at serverless computing on Microsoft Azure, covering the key concepts, benefits, and patterns of serverless applications.
What is Serverless Computing? Serverless computing allows developers to build and run applications and services without having to provision or manage any servers. The cloud service provider (in this case, Microsoft Azure) automatically provisions, scales, and manages the infrastructure required to run the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernizing Mainframe Applications with Azure- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/modernizing_mainframe_applications_with_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/modernizing_mainframe_applications_with_azure_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>As organizations strive to stay competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced digital landscape, many are considering migrating their traditional mainframe applications to the cloud. Azure, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s powerful cloud platform, offers a compelling alternative to the mainframe, providing hyperscale compute and storage in a highly available environment.
In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key strategies and considerations for making the switch from a mainframe platform to Azure.
MIPS vs. vCPUs: Mapping Mainframe Workloads to the Cloud One of the first challenges in a mainframe migration is determining the appropriate level of compute resources needed to run your workloads on Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Computing- Exploring the Benefits, Service Models, and Deployment Options</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_cloud_computing_exploring_the_benefits_service_models_and_deployment_options/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/understanding_cloud_computing_exploring_the_benefits_service_models_and_deployment_options/</guid>
      <description>Cloud computing has become an integral part of modern technology, transforming the way organizations and individuals approach computing resources. In this comprehensive article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key benefits and considerations of using cloud services, delve into the differences between Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS), Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS), and Software-as-a-Service (SaaS), and compare the public, private, and hybrid cloud deployment models.
The Benefits and Considerations of Cloud Computing Cloud computing offers a wide range of benefits that can significantly impact an organization&amp;rsquo;s operations and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Hybrid App with On-Premises Data that Scales Across Clouds</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/deploying_a_hybrid_app_with_on-premises_data_that_scales_across_clouds/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive guide shows you how to deploy a hybrid app that spans both Azure and Azure Stack Hub and uses a single on-premises data source. By using a hybrid cloud solution, you can combine the compliance benefits of a private cloud with the scalability of the public cloud. Your developers can also take advantage of the Microsoft developer ecosystem and apply their skills to the cloud and on-premises environments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
