<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure App Service on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/azure-app-service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure App Service on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/azure-app-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Migrate Assessments- Best Practices for Maximizing Migration Success</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_migrate_assessments_best_practices_for_maximizing_migration_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/mastering_azure_migrate_assessments_best_practices_for_maximizing_migration_success/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that simplifies the process of discovering, assessing, and migrating workloads to Microsoft Azure. The Azure Migrate Discovery and assessment tool is a crucial component that helps organizations evaluate their on-premises infrastructure and determine the best path forward for their cloud migration journey. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into the best practices for creating assessments using the Azure Migrate Discovery and assessment tool, ensuring you can make informed decisions and optimize your migration efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize and Manage Costs for Azure App Service</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_and_manage_costs_for_azure_app_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/optimize_and_manage_costs_for_azure_app_service/</guid>
      <description>Azure App Service is a powerful and flexible platform for hosting web applications, APIs, and mobile backends in the cloud. However, as with any cloud service, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand and manage the costs associated with using App Service. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to plan, optimize, and monitor costs for your Azure App Service deployments.
Understanding the App Service Billing Model When you use Azure App Service, you&amp;rsquo;re charged based on several factors:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
