<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintainability on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/maintainability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maintainability on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/maintainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of PowerShell- Essential Scripting Style and Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_essential_scripting_style_and_best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_essential_scripting_style_and_best_practices/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving world of PowerShell, the art of writing efficient, maintainable, and readable code is paramount. This comprehensive guide delves into the essential scripting style and best practices that can elevate your PowerShell prowess to new heights.
PowerShell, as a powerful scripting language, has become an indispensable tool for system administrators, IT professionals, and automation enthusiasts. However, with great power comes great responsibility. Adopting a set of well-defined best practices can help you navigate the intricacies of PowerShell and ensure your code is not only effective but also easily understandable and reusable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell- Best Practices for Efficient and Maintainable Scripts</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_for_efficient_and_maintainable_scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_for_efficient_and_maintainable_scripts/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell: Best Practices for Efficient and Maintainable Scripts Navigating the Diverse PowerShell Landscape As you dive into the world of PowerShell scripting, you&amp;rsquo;ll quickly realize that the PowerShell community is a diverse and opinionated one. When scanning through code projects on the PoshCode repository or the Microsoft Learn Code Samples Gallery, you&amp;rsquo;ll encounter a wide range of approaches and perspectives on what constitutes &amp;ldquo;best practices</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
