<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure SQL on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/azure-sql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure SQL on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/azure-sql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Your SQL Server and Windows Server Investments with Azure Hybrid Benefit</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/maximize_your_sql_server_and_windows_server_investments_with_azure_hybrid_benefit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/maximize_your_sql_server_and_windows_server_investments_with_azure_hybrid_benefit/</guid>
      <description>Azure Hybrid Benefit is a powerful cost-saving program from Microsoft that allows you to get more value from your existing Windows Server, SQL Server, and Linux software investments when migrating to the cloud. By applying your on-premises licenses to Azure, you can save up to 85% over standard pay-as-you-go rates and seamlessly extend your hybrid infrastructure.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how Azure Hybrid Benefit can benefit your organization:
1. Save Up to 85% on Azure Costs With Azure Hybrid Benefit, you can use your existing Windows Server and SQL Server licenses to run virtual machines in Azure at a substantially reduced rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Migrate Assessments- Best Practices for Maximizing Migration Success</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_azure_migrate_assessments_best_practices_for_maximizing_migration_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_azure_migrate_assessments_best_practices_for_maximizing_migration_success/</guid>
      <description>Azure Migrate is a powerful platform that simplifies the process of discovering, assessing, and migrating workloads to Microsoft Azure. The Azure Migrate Discovery and assessment tool is a crucial component that helps organizations evaluate their on-premises infrastructure and determine the best path forward for their cloud migration journey. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into the best practices for creating assessments using the Azure Migrate Discovery and assessment tool, ensuring you can make informed decisions and optimize your migration efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Centrally Managed Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/optimizing_centrally_managed_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_sql_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/optimizing_centrally_managed_azure_hybrid_benefit_for_sql_server/</guid>
      <description>Optimizing Centrally Managed Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of proactively managing and optimizing your use of Azure Hybrid Benefit for SQL Server. By centrally managing this benefit, you can reduce the costs of running Azure SQL and ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the most value out of your existing SQL Server licenses.
Prerequisites Before you begin, make sure you have:
  Read and understood the What is centrally managed Azure Hybrid Benefit?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
