<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud Cost Optimization on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/cloud-cost-optimization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud Cost Optimization on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/cloud-cost-optimization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Azure Cost Management for Partners</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_azure_cost_management_for_partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/getting_started_with_azure_cost_management_for_partners/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with Azure Cost Management for Partners As a Microsoft partner, Azure Cost Management is a powerful tool that can help you effectively manage and monitor your customers&#39; cloud costs. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the key features and capabilities of Cost Management, and how you can leverage them to gain visibility, control, and optimization of your customers&#39; Azure spending.
Understanding Cost Management Scopes In Cost Management, there are two main types of scopes: billing scopes and Azure RBAC scopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Savings and Efficiency with Microsoft Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_savings_and_efficiency_with_microsoft_cost_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/maximize_savings_and_efficiency_with_microsoft_cost_management/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Cost Management is a powerful suite of FinOps tools that help organizations like yours analyze, monitor, and optimize their Microsoft Cloud costs. With Cost Management, you can gain visibility into your cloud spending, proactively manage your budget, and identify opportunities to optimize and streamline your cloud infrastructure.
One of the key features of Cost Management is its ability to help you organize and allocate your cloud costs. By leveraging tools like billing profiles, invoice sections, management groups, and resource tags, you can ensure that costs are accurately attributed to the right business units and projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gain Cost Visibility and Accountability with Azure Cost Allocation</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/gain_cost_visibility_and_accountability_with_azure_cost_allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/gain_cost_visibility_and_accountability_with_azure_cost_allocation/</guid>
      <description>As organizations increasingly rely on Azure to power their digital transformation, managing and understanding cloud costs becomes a critical priority. This is especially true for large enterprises that centrally manage Azure services or resources, while different internal departments or business units consume them. The centrally managing team often wants to reallocate the cost of the shared services back out to the internal departments or organizational business units who are actively using the services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
