<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reusability on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/reusability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reusability on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/reusability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Power of PowerShell- Essential Scripting Style and Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_essential_scripting_style_and_best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/unlock_the_power_of_powershell_essential_scripting_style_and_best_practices/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-evolving world of PowerShell, the art of writing efficient, maintainable, and readable code is paramount. This comprehensive guide delves into the essential scripting style and best practices that can elevate your PowerShell prowess to new heights.
PowerShell, as a powerful scripting language, has become an indispensable tool for system administrators, IT professionals, and automation enthusiasts. However, with great power comes great responsibility. Adopting a set of well-defined best practices can help you navigate the intricacies of PowerShell and ensure your code is not only effective but also easily understandable and reusable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell Best Practices- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/mastering_powershell_best_practices_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell Best Practices: A Comprehensive Guide Introduction As a seasoned PowerShell practitioner, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the diverse perspectives and practices within the PowerShell community. From code projects on PoshCode to the Microsoft Learn Code Samples Gallery, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that PowerShell users have a wide range of opinions on what constitutes &amp;ldquo;right and wrong</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
