<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Least Privilege on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/least-privilege/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Least Privilege on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/least-privilege/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Securing Azure Container Instances- A Comprehensive Approach</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_a_comprehensive_approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_a_comprehensive_approach/</guid>
      <description>Securing Azure Container Instances: A Comprehensive Approach Containers have become an increasingly popular way to package and deploy applications, but they also come with unique security challenges. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key security considerations for running container workloads on Azure Container Instances (ACI) and provide practical recommendations to help you secure your container ecosystem.
Use a Private Container Registry Container images are the foundation of your container-based applications, so it&amp;rsquo;s critical to ensure their security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing Azure Container Instances- Best Practices for Image Management and Container Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_best_practices_for_image_management_and_container_ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/securing_azure_container_instances_best_practices_for_image_management_and_container_ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>Securing Azure Container Instances: Best Practices for Image Management and Container Ecosystem Containerizing your applications can bring tremendous benefits in terms of portability, scalability, and efficiency. However, it also introduces new security considerations that must be addressed to protect your Azure infrastructure and workloads. This comprehensive guide explores the key security recommendations for managing container images and the broader container ecosystem when using Azure Container Instances.
Secure Your Container Images Use a Private Container Registry Storing and retrieving container images from a private registry, such as Azure Container Registry or Docker Trusted Registry, is crucial for mitigating security risks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
