<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SD-WAN on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/sd-wan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SD-WAN on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/sd-wan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Virtual WAN- A Comprehensive Guide for Seamless Site-to-Site Connectivity</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/mastering_azure_virtual_wan_a_comprehensive_guide_for_seamless_site-to-site_connectivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/mastering_azure_virtual_wan_a_comprehensive_guide_for_seamless_site-to-site_connectivity/</guid>
      <description>Mastering Azure Virtual WAN: A Comprehensive Guide for Seamless Site-to-Site Connectivity Azure Virtual WAN is a powerful and versatile networking service that simplifies the process of connecting your on-premises sites to Azure resources. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned networking professional or new to the cloud, this comprehensive guide will walk you through the step-by-step process of creating a secure, reliable, and scalable site-to-site connection using Virtual WAN.
Understanding Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a fully managed, software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) service that provides unified connectivity and security across your global network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Your Local Sites to Azure Using Azure Virtual WAN</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/connecting_your_local_sites_to_azure_using_azure_virtual_wan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/connecting_your_local_sites_to_azure_using_azure_virtual_wan/</guid>
      <description>Azure Virtual WAN is a networking service that provides a simple, unified, and global connectivity solution for connecting your on-premises sites to Azure. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how you can leverage Virtual WAN to establish secure site-to-site VPN connections between your local network and your Azure resources.
Understanding Azure Virtual WAN Azure Virtual WAN is a fully managed, software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) service that simplifies the process of connecting your branch offices, retail locations, and other remote sites to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
