<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Functions on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/functions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Functions on mangoldai :: cloud architect insights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Serverless Computing on Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_on_microsoft_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/exploring_serverless_computing_on_microsoft_azure/</guid>
      <description>Serverless computing is a revolutionary approach to application development that enables developers to build and run applications without having to manage any underlying infrastructure. This article provides an in-depth look at serverless computing on Microsoft Azure, covering the key concepts, benefits, and patterns of serverless applications.
What is Serverless Computing? Serverless computing allows developers to build and run applications and services without having to provision or manage any servers. The cloud service provider (in this case, Microsoft Azure) automatically provisions, scales, and manages the infrastructure required to run the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering PowerShell- A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/mastering_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/mastering_powershell_a_comprehensive_guide/</guid>
      <description>Mastering PowerShell: A Comprehensive Guide PowerShell is a powerful and versatile scripting language that has become an essential tool for system administrators, developers, and IT professionals. This comprehensive guide will take you on a journey to explore the various features and capabilities of PowerShell, helping you become a proficient PowerShell user.
Basic Commands Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the fundamentals of PowerShell. PowerShell provides a set of built-in commands, known as Cmdlets, that are written in .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
