<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Active Directory on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/active-directory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Active Directory on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/tags/active-directory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Your Hybrid Identity Environment with Microsoft Defender for Identity</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/protecting_your_hybrid_identity_environment_with_microsoft_defender_for_identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/protecting_your_hybrid_identity_environment_with_microsoft_defender_for_identity/</guid>
      <description>Protecting Your Hybrid Identity Environment with Microsoft Defender for Identity Microsoft Defender for Identity (MDI) is a powerful tool that plays a critical role in safeguarding your hybrid identity environment. As a component of the Microsoft 365 Defender suite, MDI gathers signals from on-premises Active Directory servers and uses these signals to protect your organization against hackers who attempt to leverage compromised accounts to move laterally across your on-premises workstations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickly Deploy Microsoft Defender for Identity Sensors on Active Directory and Other Key Servers</title>
      <link>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/quickly_deploy_microsoft_defender_for_identity_sensors_on_active_directory_and_other_key_servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmangold23.github.io/mangoldaiwiki/posts/quickly_deploy_microsoft_defender_for_identity_sensors_on_active_directory_and_other_key_servers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Identity is a critical security solution that helps protect your organization against identity-based attacks. This comprehensive guide will walk you through the quick installation process to get your Defender for Identity sensors up and running on your Active Directory, Active Directory Federation Services (AD FS), and Active Directory Certificate Services (AD CS) servers.
Prerequisites Before you begin the installation, it&amp;rsquo;s important to ensure you have the necessary prerequisites in place:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
