<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Defender on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</title>
    <link>https://mangoldai.com/tags/azure-defender/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Defender on Cloud architect insights :: Joshua Mangold</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mangoldai.com/tags/azure-defender/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Securing Your Azure Containers with Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/securing_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/securing_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a comprehensive cloud-native solution that helps you improve, monitor, and maintain the security of your containerized assets across multicloud and on-premises environments. This includes Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images.
To get started with Defender for Containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a Microsoft Azure subscription. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you can sign up for a free Azure subscription. You&amp;rsquo;ll also need to enable Microsoft Defender for Cloud on your Azure subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your Azure Containers with Defender for Containers</title>
      <link>https://mangoldai.com/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mangoldai.com/posts/secure_your_azure_containers_with_defender_for_containers/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Containers is a powerful cloud-native solution that helps organizations improve, monitor, and maintain the security of their containerized assets across multi-cloud and on-premises environments. This comprehensive platform protects Kubernetes clusters, nodes, workloads, container registries, and container images, ensuring the security and resilience of your containerized applications.
Enabling Defender for Containers To get started with Defender for Containers, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a few prerequisites:
 Azure Subscription: You&amp;rsquo;ll need an active Microsoft Azure subscription.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
